<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165001">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/0oKjM-NrnTQNeQZrnhyxRGOSdig=/fit-in/200x150/pic2226102.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/u47Y1_zbtF3ezKbt8rWz6W8AnE8=/0x0/pic2226102.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Tenocha: Heroic Adventures" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="25750" value="Tenocha: Heroic Adventures" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;TENOCHA IS a slowly collapsing accord of city-states, occupying a jungle-covered continent that is populated primarily by humans and mostly-humans.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;IT IS A PLACE WHERE some things are very different.  Most significant property is owned by clans rather than individuals.  There are people with elemental powers, and people with scales, living on every street &amp;ndash; and their powers are directly incorporated into industry and life.  And Tenochans, while having the same degree of physical sexual diversity as real people, often marry in groups, and sort themselves into three base genders, rather than two (man, woman, arha).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;IT IS A PLACE WITH PROBLEMS.  Just off the eastern coast of Tenocha lies the reach, an island chain ruled by dragons and with whom Tenocha is perpetually at war.  It has enemies inside; cults operate in secret across Tenocha, calling up diabolical entities to bind or worship. It is built on an unstable base; the magical industries of the region are powered by decaying artifacts, which cannot be repaired or replaced easily.  And it is stratified - Status is based on age, class, race, and gender, in a system vastly different from our own, but still one that is deeply imperfect and unequal.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Note: THIS IS A LIVING DOCUMENT. It might be updated every week for a month at some point; it might sit dormant for a few years.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="37184" value="Tenocha Fantasy Setting" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2107" value="Campaign Setting (game world)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2121" value="Action Table (table determines action outcomes)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2680" value="Dice (Primarily Fudge/dF)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2120" value="Dice Pool (Roll multiple dice vs target)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2098" value="Trait / Aspect Based (personality affects gameplay)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="10510" value="Amagi Games" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="24900" value="Levi Kornelsen" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="24900" value="Levi Kornelsen" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="24900" value="Levi Kornelsen" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>