<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165193">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/TJys1PvjD85sBmZItPkIVHCzZbA=/fit-in/200x150/pic3145705.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/rGAfi7jVFcyivb3kgmWpjR__XGI=/0x0/pic3145705.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Men in Black Introductory Adventure Game" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="910" value="Men in Black: The Roleplaying Game" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From the back of the box: &amp;#10;You've seen Men in Black... Now Live the Adventure!&amp;#10;Investigate the crash landing of an alien holofim superstar. Fend off crazed UFO conspiracy nuts. Battle hairy, hungry, tooth-filled aliens. Use Series 4 de-atomizers, Korlian XT-17s, and the infamous Noisy Cricket to keep those aliens in line and protect the innocent Earthlings from the real truth about aliens living on this planet.&amp;#10;You can do all this and more with the Men in Black Introductory Adventure Game.&amp;#10;This game has everything you need to create your own make-believe missions as Men in Black agents. You and your friends can pretend to be agents protecting the Earth from the scum of the universe-all you need is this game and your imagination.&amp;#10;This game teaches you the rules while you play. One game booklet shows how to create and use your own customised MiB agent. Another booklet teaches one person, the Director, how to run other players through exciting Men in Black assignments. It also includes an overview of the equipment and weapons the Men in Black use and the aliens they encounter. A book of missions lets you and your friends save the Earth from power hungry aliens. Maps of popular locations, illustrated cards, and character stand-ups help visualize the action and create your own missions.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This box includes:&amp;#10;-An Agent's Guide which begins teaching the rules as soon as you start reading.&amp;#10;-Several Character Sheets you can choose from to customize and play your very own MiB agent.&amp;#10;-A Director's Guide with information on the mysterious Men in Black&amp;#10;-A MiB Mission Book in which you help stop an evil alien plot against Earth.&amp;#10;-6 Dice&amp;#10;-16 Color Cards showing aliens, equipment and weapons used in Men in Black assignments.&amp;#10;-Stand-Up Characters to help play out the action&amp;#10;-4 Maps illustrating typical Men in Black locations, such as  remote farm-houses and alien crash-landing sites.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="1997" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="185" value="Comedy / Satire" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="550" value="Modern" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="183" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2622" value="Quick Start / Fast Play Rules" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2120" value="Dice Pool (Roll multiple dice vs target)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2100" value="Point Based (allocate points to get skills, powers, etc)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="40" value="West End Games" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="10900" value="Peter Schweighofer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="13822" value="Nikola Vrtis" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="14836" value="Joe Bavitz" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="13604" value="Tim Bobko" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="12072" value="Steve Bryant" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="13821" value="Fred Jandt" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="11989" value="Brian Schomburg" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="15032" value="Jen Seiden" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="13475" value="George R. Strayton" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="2" />
			<average value="5" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="1" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="8" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>