<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165202">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/xWofPcEs6lemt1o5eUlMFlUZMG0=/fit-in/200x150/pic2228393.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/_pF9oOYd7IUSEfoHuLpUE5a1Kew=/0x0/pic2228393.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Lair of the Daashiono" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The City By the Sea is a complicated city. Long ago the god presence living there drew the Daashiono to it and they settled in the sea caves beneath the city. Harboring tiny god bits gone astray, the Daashiono are first and foremost creators, but the god spark in them went bad. Now they experiment and create with human flesh in the great sea caves that offer them the secrecy they need to make monsters. Over the years the Daashiono have proliferated and from the tunnels and sea caves they have migrated through sewers and basements to access every part of the city. They bargain and negotiate for human flesh with slavers, thieves and with isolationists disappearing northerners.  Daashiono themselves are hunted too. Specialized forces, people who may have seen their families and towns destroyed by them, want to eliminate them all. And the university intellectuals study them. Who are they? Where did they come from? What can be done about them?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2012" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #048" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>