<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165250">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/tZg726Y_DwZbY2kpuQ50obJUoQg=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229420.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/r8e298TS0z3sNORYLTbXm9CTQhw=/0x0/pic2229420.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Lowmoon Valley" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;So Beautiful! You could live here forever. That&amp;rsquo;s what Ansel Mardain thought when the Elf King sent him to explore the Lowmoon Valley. Here, where the Moonshield River widens and slows, large expansive fields of grass grow tall as two dwarves and stretch from one steep canyon wall to the other. And the mushrooms! Buttery, rich - mushrooms everywhere. Enough to keep you alive forever. !Not! These are puppet-making, Broshly Mushrooms, intent, cunning, conniving. They will trap you. They will sift their tiny mycelium spores down upon your cheeks and into your knuckle bones and you too will become a glorious hill of magnificent mushrooms, buttery and rich. It&amp;rsquo;s the dark tide that corrupted these mushrooms. If you play it right, you might survive. But, stay together, and - don&amp;rsquo;t trust the natives.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #064" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>