<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165222">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/XtvgaKTLilTcXAYiZvui6JyB_GI=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229417.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/zisbYw4YujjDJyggEwREakRcfQg=/0x0/pic2229417.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Royal Palace" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;King Krister IV has a reputation and it&amp;rsquo;s not such a good one. He&amp;rsquo;s a womanizer and everyone knows he likes to party. But his City By the Sea is on the brink of war and contrary to what many of his people believe, he is quite prepared to deal with it. That is, he&amp;rsquo;s prepared to deal with the problems he knows about. He doesn&amp;rsquo;t know that all the threads in the mix - the northerners, the military, the poor, the isolationists, the Daashiono, the Wraith King and the Troglodytes &amp;ndash; all these strands have been woven together by the young god who is poised to come into his own right now, right here in The City By the Sea. Prophecy and destiny have a bead on your city, King Krister. Brave adventurers are heading your way to fight for the young god. It looks like war! War coming to The City By the Sea&amp;hellip;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2012" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #052" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>