<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165227">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/AVBxIe-hBBLsM9g5d1R6OPhORjw=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229410.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/lZEF12l9MjX5-2YS4afnTyFnGVY=/0x0/pic2229410.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Grand Conservatory" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Musicians make good spies. They travel. They hobnob with the nobility and they&amp;rsquo;ve got minds trained to read code. Everyone thinks the Grand Conservatory in the Elf King&amp;rsquo;s old kingdom is just a beautiful music school, but unbeknownst to most, the school supports itself selling information.  Sife&amp;rsquo;s an undercover cop at the school trying to pass as one of the kids. She came looking for information about Justine Belidnine from #55 who Sife thinks stole her king&amp;rsquo;s jewels. But now Sife&amp;rsquo;s distracted. She&amp;rsquo;s not as young as she hopes she looks and the music school is far more complicated than she ever dreamed. Besides, she loves that parasitic instrument that makes her sound so great. So Sife&amp;rsquo;s on a tightrope. She&amp;rsquo;s dancing between a plague of fast aging and an explosion of parasites. She might just self-destruct.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #057" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>