<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165278">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/FGWyiU3WB7Q1YWZKN8BEnxC0cMk=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229378.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/svW2yk4xMQzTEHj92_Q94Oje1-c=/0x0/pic2229378.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Stone Shepherds Lake" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Stones float at Stone Shepherds Lake. The water glows. It&amp;rsquo;s odd. But nothing exists in a vacuum, so it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a big surprise that the lake water might be keeping the Sky Island s afloat. That&amp;rsquo;s Tonstin&amp;rsquo;s theory, and he&amp;rsquo;s an expert on the ancient battle that changed the geography of the Moonshield forever.  Now a new altercation is headed for center stage. It&amp;rsquo;s all about Princess Mishana who fled when her dad got booted. She hunkered down at the lake for years - drank the water, too. Now she&amp;rsquo;s an iron maiden, floral in appearance, but tough enough to perforate a man with a single punch, armor and all.  She wants her Dad&amp;rsquo;s throne back and it looks like she&amp;rsquo;ll get it - but only with help. Your role? Stay on her good side, for sure. Sign up. Sip the water. Tough up. Win.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #087" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77798" value="Bobby Wiessenberg" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>