<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165261">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/_6KcE11--8XOHtJ9n6-l48VN5Fw=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229393.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/tjACqkFb1WCvlMOWuqQOiuotd3Y=/0x0/pic2229393.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Well of Hours" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Hate to break it to you, folks. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not what you&amp;rsquo;d choose, but you&amp;rsquo;ve got a role in the great chess game of the future. First step? Go to the Well of Hours. You&amp;rsquo;ll find all of time there, past and future. Be sure you know which gate to take and if you decide to use the Ghost Wind? !!!Read Instructions First!!! You&amp;rsquo;d rather find a safe place? A good place to hide out? Then hide as someone doddering and incompetent like a House Delphine mage. They wrote the script on that ploy. But get going. The finger of history is pointing at you. Pull on your boots. Jump into the space where every possibility exists. Scared? Then go with Fredric. He&amp;rsquo;s a game guy. Knows how to have fun, too. Knows how to get a job done.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #074" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>