<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165221">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/h6_s-jFECk1GmxXiBE_sWmOpkts=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229418.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/7rwe7qsYOFhmQr5yrF4Zkk4bw1E=/0x0/pic2229418.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Poet&#039;s Hut" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Peace on Earth has been in the works forever, and Sheldrian Cloudsinger has been working on it almost that long. But now Poet Cloudsinger&amp;rsquo;s efforts to fix the world is getting the black god of anger worked up and Orc Chieftain, Defric Ran&amp;rsquo;drag, has decided the Poet must die. On Defric&amp;rsquo;s side he&amp;rsquo;s got his sometime lover and full time assassin, Volk of the solid black eyes. On the Cloudsinger&amp;rsquo;s side is Grastlian, the dwarf with the singing axe. From his Poet&amp;rsquo;s Hut, strung and chinked with melodic bits, the power of the Poet streams through it all. The party can gain permanent power at the hut if they manage to add to The Poet&amp;rsquo;s song, so, everybody, listen up. The wind will stir the song fragments and teach the way to go. But remember, basically it&amp;rsquo;s  a soul trip so celebrate Peace. Pick up your own Singing Dwarven Axe. Boost the flag! It&amp;rsquo;s Power to the Peaceful!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2012" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #051" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>