<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165267">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/n2PHZteVKZ-3KV_uGCW3Zz5T-R8=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229388.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/eqZ7dqemQytvq_cGJrGi1dhHSF4=/0x0/pic2229388.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Spice Merchant&#039;s Shop" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Kingdoms rise and fall in predictable ways if you know what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for. Amoustad Dubba, Spice Merchant is a student of patterns. He sees how the ways of the world grow out the realities later called history. Just like the past, Toys for the Sandbox is one long saga and with #79 a new feature lets you trace the patterns. A reference section gives you fingertip access to &amp;ldquo;who is that?&amp;rdquo;and &amp;ldquo;when did that happen&amp;rdquo; information and gives you the ability to fill in the holes where you missed something or forgot. In this issue you&amp;rsquo;ll find spices and poisons sitting side by side in the colored bottles on the Spice Merchant&amp;rsquo;s Shelves. So be careful. Make sure your mind doesn&amp;rsquo;t explode mistaking Dead Monkey Root for Ginseng. Or maybe just listen. Those old guys? Wow! History is moving on. Might as well get the download.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #079" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77798" value="Bobby Wiessenberg" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>