<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165263">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/xoprVY1_H0CA4VGMASrCOd8Fn40=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229392.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/mMMvivdO4uzYopBY1pBfwWyz2zo=/0x0/pic2229392.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Rusted Vale" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Outside the gates of the Elf King&amp;rsquo;s palace, Kryzcazzca still holds court from inside the Emperor&amp;rsquo;s preserved head. Filthy rain and soot fall constantly and drizzle down to the valley below. The soil is red with rust. This erstwhile green and bustling valley is now The Rusted Vale. Soul locusts live here, burrow wights, too. And scavengers, but barely, living hand to mouth. Abbot Eister knows it&amp;rsquo;s time to evict Kryzcazzca and he needs adventurers to help. !Please help! But keep safe and watch out for distractions. There are lots of leftovers of death hanging on around here. Don&amp;rsquo;t get drawn in when spectral soldiers fight on moonless nights. Avoid the territorial, aggressive piles of scrap that actually are soul locusts intent to destroy you. And, one last caution? Watch out for the Junk Man. He wants firsties on everything. He hopes you die.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #075" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>