<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="165288">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Don Bradman Cricket 14" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>The game features a number of different game modes, including a career mode, custom matches and online games. The career mode involves a user creating a player and playing matches in order for their player to progress. A users player starts at the age of 16 and has a maximum of a 20 year career. There is also a Cricket Academy program in which a user can create and edit teams, players and competitions. This was released as a stand alone game before the console release date. Big Ant Studios updated the academy and brought the 'Practice Nets' feature into it in the weeks prior to the launch of the full game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The gameplay features were announced as having &amp;quot;Unique Batting and Bowling Controls&amp;quot; with a full 360 shot delivery with no shot markers. The gameplay also involves a &amp;quot;Fully featured Fielding System&amp;quot; which allows &amp;quot;full control of the field&amp;quot;. The Ball Physics in the game has been labelled as having &amp;quot;realistic edges and ball movement off players&amp;quot;. Appeal and Electric Reviews have also been included into the game, which enables a user to challenge the umpire for a decision in which is questionable. There are Practice nets and Match practice which are new features to the game and are supposed to help a new 'cricketing gamer' to play the game. Users can also save games online and offline. The commentary team consists of Matthew Hill and David Basheer.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The game includes 79 teams within the game, most of which are unlicensed. There are international and domestic teams (current generation) historical teams and future generation teams. There are 17 international teams, 6 Australian domestic teams, 18 English domestic, along with &amp;quot;All time best&amp;quot; teams and &amp;quot;historical&amp;quot; teams.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There are 11 unlicensed grounds within the game, with 2 licensed.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: Wikipedia, &amp;quot;Don Bradman Cricket 14&amp;quot;, available under the CC-BY-SA License.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2156" value="Simulation" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2157" value="Sports" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2405" value="Sports - Other" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameseries" id="39405" value="Don Bradman Cricket" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2310" value="Network Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="0" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-06-26" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="14166" value="Big Ant Studios" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="14166" value="Big Ant Studios" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="1" />
			<average value="7.5" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="3" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>