<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165260">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/w--YGm2YyxPRbADH2516tybyjTk=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229394.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/hCwCwOUd75xQuE3lLJ5AVG2qeeo=/0x0/pic2229394.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Court of the Slave Lord" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If you know the way, never say so. If you&amp;rsquo;ve seen it with your own eyes, deny it. That&amp;rsquo;s the way the Slave Lord wants it. Don&amp;rsquo;t ever tell where the Court of the Slave Lord is. He might use his Will Taker on you and shove you through your paces anyway he wants forever. He&amp;rsquo;s a bad guy, but be warned, he&amp;rsquo;s got good magic. Take a look at those henchmen of his. He made the bird guy himself. That guy, for all his chirping good humor, is the spell brother to the chain golem on the Slave Lord&amp;rsquo;s other side. Hatchet men and counselors both. No milk of human kindness here. So, if fighting evil&amp;rsquo;s your gig - step right up. You found it. It&amp;rsquo;s here. Toys #73.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #073" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>