<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165266">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/jb5DIFmHeF8LWp24xVSzU4_ZWRI=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229389.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/pqY43Zgfw57YnHO0K_G97wQNyBE=/0x0/pic2229389.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Island of Ancient Skulls" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In #78, they&amp;rsquo;re all in cahoots. The Demon King, the Blood Mages, the Godslayer. Best to hook up with powers outside yourself and get that extra edge. Markontis has a demon sidekick he&amp;rsquo;s had since he was a kid. Authric studies holy books and Steelhamer trusts revelation. The Godslayer meddles in all of it and the savants in the Woodsman&amp;rsquo;s Cabin braid it all together to predict the future. It&amp;rsquo;s all too big a picture to ever comprehend all of it, but there are smaller gigs you can pick up to shove the arrows of time in one precise way or another. Try to find an Angel Tongue, a blade that keeps the dark at bay, and get in there with the guys holding the black stuff back. Or play a bad guy? See what grows out. You&amp;rsquo;re in the mix already. Make your mark. Make history.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #078" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>