<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165270">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/Ozsh06qgZiZoQlQsSeHNkKIFf4A=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229387.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/Fb7iRtdctFgmSuCTKCvDWJVG7Ng=/0x0/pic2229387.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Chapel of Three Swords" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If it&amp;rsquo;s so easy, is it even important? That&amp;rsquo;s what Devlin asks himself. But what does he know? He&amp;rsquo;s just a gifted mage, coddled by his god. Does he have a true faith that will survive the battle that everyone says is coming? The Demon King is frothing to be free and Shiel Reborn is mustered right behind him. It all depends on you to ring the changes that bring this saga to the next step. So saddle up. Devlin&amp;rsquo;s got the power, but needs some guidance. Revolutionary Srin is back from #53, but don&amp;rsquo;t forget, she&amp;rsquo;s the same gene pool as the God King. Trust her if you dare. She&amp;rsquo;s the friend of Apstillias, the Sword of Knowledge, so you decide. Good Luck. The fate of the world is in this uneasy cloud and your world will soon be getting wet.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #080" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77798" value="Bobby Wiessenberg" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>