<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165259">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/mZHEFq8PhAmN638RzWUh9yjaLgI=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229395.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/KZE73IUklABWegboFMQPYM0ksvU=/0x0/pic2229395.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Stone Demon Pits" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is the home of House Mitrain. This is the home of the Stone Demon Pits that birthed the three hundred foot tall demons towering on the landscape. Some demons stand, some sit, some march. Heveric Hoblinhouse thinks she can control the demon called Des-mogoth with a Demon Rider&amp;rsquo;s Rod. Her qualifications? She discovered a famine-busting bread made of lichen and dandelion and ended up the last one standing. Heveric is just a fulcrum of history and will need a lot of help. Beware though. There are weird, little stone constructs from fairyland that like to steal children ducking in and out and around the pits, as well as mean, minor demons eager to create something nasty. You&amp;rsquo;ll find some Stone Armor here. Use it. The Moonshield was cozy compared to these Demon Pits.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #072" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>