<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165264">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/_A5gifWgRy4yb1tnP8LgySxUcsg=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229391.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/NhF2PS6WKJYk0p67tVBGZMB3HLY=/0x0/pic2229391.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The House with No Doors" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Mages of House Vour live in The House With No Doors. In fact, they made it. They&amp;rsquo;re a group of mages who broke away from other houses and started their own. Lacking the imprimatur of the Emperor of Shiel put them in a bad light for awhile, but the cool stuff they construct is changing that. How about a house where the rooms come when called? How about a construct that cleans clothes? Yes, once they made nasty things, but no need to bring up the past. Now House Vour works for the betterment of mankind. You hear about those Guard Mice? Sleep the night away? Don&amp;rsquo;t even stand guard. You say there are war golems in the vault below? Don&amp;rsquo;t give them another thought. No Doors means no one can get at them anyway. Right? Oops, you say, wrong? You&amp;rsquo;re sooo correct! Put some mice in your pocket. Save #76!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #076" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>