<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165246">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/6J1mouCA4NCM9TsC5uJgi8T-25I=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229407.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/CvY8oD-EHB1zlMz-CdPu4N8WYM8=/0x0/pic2229407.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Temple of the Dead God" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If you&amp;rsquo;re not an adventurer, don&amp;rsquo;t even try this. But, yes, this is the entrance, this is the door. Take the rope at the top of the canyon &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;ll drop you straight down to the temple of the dead god &amp;ndash; some say a god outside of time. No matter. The temple&amp;rsquo;s outside time too, but trust the rope. It&amp;rsquo;ll make the trip. Once you get to the temple you&amp;rsquo;ll see some toys pieces you&amp;rsquo;ve met before slotting into place. The Old Fool and the Elf King are here, and some cloistered undead too, all watched over by Velistina, a friend of Edward Fulton, the captain of the Astral Star. She&amp;rsquo;s watching for shenanigans the Godslayer might pull trying to escape from Pirate Island. Don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled. He&amp;rsquo;ll use this door if he can. And if he can slay a god, what might he do to flesh like you?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #060" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>