<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165226">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/5f97WtKYxzAk9rYXQZjzclDYHR4=/fit-in/200x150/pic2229412.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/Sex9s2qJQYPBaJteRY1HXPpJ2X0=/0x0/pic2229412.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Moonshield Falls" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Hold on! Vision adjustment! Moonshield Falls is a nice piece of real estate, but training an army here? Those Rebirth of Shiel people just don&amp;rsquo;t get it. Moonshield Falls is where it all began! The Sun and the Moon duked it out for control of the world right here where the falls are now and, at the same time, in the most inadvertent of fashions, left their progeny, Shamu Nanna, behind. Shamu Nanna&amp;rsquo;s  a little hard to describe as he&amp;rsquo;s a hybrid of metal and tendrils and vines. The God Slayer did a number on him too with an extra dose of super sentience. But you&amp;rsquo;ll recognize him when you see him. He&amp;rsquo;ll be the one teaching the teachers. For you, personally? The big thing about Shamu Nanna is that he&amp;rsquo;s his own source of divine magic, and if you check him out, you can plug right in. Join the cause, maybe? Fight those Elf King lovers! Yeah!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #056" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77767" value="Bill Stanton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>