<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165334">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/LQkNjyM5J1h1NEZ4WR17YwieYF4=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230256.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/PArgOKShTGEK-qoEkxsvjBmDpXs=/0x0/pic2230256.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Palace of the Dragon Prince" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys #100 - This issue is the key. It ties up all the connections, ties them up with a bow. Eww! That&amp;rsquo;s not a bow! That&amp;rsquo;s a succubus. Winsome, yes, approachable, beguiling - Crylas by name. But, quick, if you touched her - suck and spit! Just don&amp;rsquo;t get distracted. See, over there? Dragon like and princely, holding aloft the dragon armors of Mercy and Rage? It&amp;rsquo;s the Dragon Prince balancing out onto the blade of history. He&amp;rsquo;s just a fragment of god stuff himself, still wrapped in corruption, but ready to wake his brothers, the Six Great Dragons and take on the Demon King. Help him. Help the Dragon Prince vanquish The Corruption the Godslayer visited on the world. You&amp;rsquo;ll be able to fight past death itself when you don the armor. And one more thing? Forsake pleasure. Pleasure is a demon&amp;rsquo;s tool. Not for heroes&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #100" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>