<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165379">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/vQMMMCuc_B30HuZ9AVV5PndNlqU=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230372.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/TYzNyQvE6QGOUVNeIpruR0OoQY0=/0x0/pic2230372.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Timeless Waste" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;When time stands still you don&amp;rsquo;t have to sleep and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to eat. That means travel light - leave your bed roll behind. Just bring yourself to the Timeless Waste where you&amp;rsquo;re needed to keep the world on an even keel. You&amp;rsquo;ve got a bad disease like lycanthropy? Then timelessness is a good thing. You won&amp;rsquo;t have another full moon to suffer through. But timelessness opens wiggle room for the bad guys to get back to the past and manipulate the squeakers of history they lost. Hind sight is 20/20, they say, and corrupted dragon fighters are going to sneak through and use it. Want to refight the War of Corruption? That would be a bad thing, or so thinks Dragon legionnaire, Dealth standing forever at the gate of the Timeless Waste. Listen up. He&amp;rsquo;s calling for reinforcements. Calling you. Prop up the status quo. Please. Now.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #129" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>