<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165316">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/jr6B7tZhHZK2SILSg_Gmzr25HDA=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230072.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/iOIYYX3UB2ft0FAic0-9WMo7cZY=/0x0/pic2230072.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Toys for the Sandbox Special #1" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys has taken some amazing turns in the last hundred-plus issues and, at bargain prices, hot summer days beg for a revisit to some of its roots. In this four issue Toys treasury, the Apothecary introduces what becomes an ongoing theme of herbs and poisons and spells. Supernatural creatures arrive in the first issues as well and holy men and prophecy announce themselves. Also included in these first four plots is the initial pub story, The Gryphon Gambling, launching a good fun theme that repeats every several months. Next week&amp;rsquo;s issue (#130) is a pub issue, featuring Halfling  spies plotting to put the Elves and their inflated ideas of their own superiority in their place.  Want to investigate levitating mining camps? Outmaneuver plotting mushrooms? Make the acquaintance of kamikaze rabbits, ears tied back for combat? Be charmed by a master storyteller? This is Toys. This is where Toys started.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="60426" value="Ashe Ryder" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>