<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165373">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/vmoGRYtC5ocH2yb59RP0PqwFWIU=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230378.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/IqK1iiUqJ1QrsrhM-FrqQFgd1dw=/0x0/pic2230378.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Low Road" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Grootslag has been a power below the Horidian Waste for eons, but the Low Road takes you through his domain and you&amp;rsquo;re going to have to deal with him. Pulling down magical energy from the waste above and from the ulgdain spirits he wallows in, the Grootslag has been making clumsy, elephant-headed spider troops for ages. But no worry, they are not smart, and Mowdain the Red will be on your side. He is seriously studying on eliminating the Grootslag altogether - his weird invented minions too. Mowdain himself is dangerous, of course, but if you want to be a hero? Don&amp;rsquo;t wait for a miracle. Mowdain will lead you into trouble, possibly grief, but if you are motivated to obliterate this ugly Grootslag thing, this is your best bet. Depend on Grounding Irons to discharge the magic of the waste. Other than that? You&amp;rsquo;re on your own.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #123" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>