<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165359">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Oiler&#039;s Cup" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;When the colonists came to Port Morganti, only some were in the know. Those who weren&amp;rsquo;t got slaughtered. Now the Faith of the Five is in full denial &amp;ndash; even building a temple with its bloody hands. The game plan is to keep mum about the massacre. But Riselian Hawkins, proprietor of the Oilers&amp;rsquo; Cup, is suspicious.  Tongues slip. He hears. There are survivors, too. That girl who waits tables? She witnessed her father die. Now the satyr, Bryn, is bringing her two heads a night - an effort to identify the guy who did it. So here&amp;rsquo;s the plan. Stop the satyr&amp;rsquo;s slaughter first. Then set up some simple law and order. And stay out of the fairy circle. Keep clear of the church basement too and the portal there to the astral plane. Neither&amp;rsquo;s marked, but there&amp;rsquo;s a map. Keep it simple. Clean the place up.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #110" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>