<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165372">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/VNmunHwX-UB77nVOWfiEOZguses=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230374.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/OILMC0Z_7y-WvEZqNSwA4Zizd2U=/0x0/pic2230374.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Crèche of the Storm Elves" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;All storm elves get born in a cr&amp;egrave;che - but don&amp;rsquo;t think Christmas and Jesus in the manger. Think vats of harvested body parts in amniotic fluid, primed with heroes&amp;rsquo; blood. You&amp;rsquo;ll meet the Harvester in #122. He&amp;rsquo;s a cool guy. Always happy and a master of his work. He keeps his scalpels sharp, and carves to prolong life as long as possible. Nothing wrong with that, though the unquiet souls do stack up. Roco is on their side. He belongs to the Order of Sleep, and yes he&amp;rsquo;s a necromancer, but his strongest desire is to bring peace to the undead. He and his sheep are going to take on the ovoid, black-glass cr&amp;egrave;che. He will need protection. You will too, but Roco knows some tricks. And all those kids? Cr&amp;egrave;che kids stay in the cr&amp;egrave;che until they&amp;rsquo;re grown. Saving them is up to you. Ready or not.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #122" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="3" value="(Uncredited)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>