<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165363">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/c2hBs1xF81Tr59bFTtXl0Dl03P0=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230341.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/scUS6Lm8_9wPSeAw7eWyaFjRorI=/0x0/pic2230341.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Iron Wall" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Iron Wall harbors some strange characters. But, hey. It&amp;rsquo;s never fallen and even though it&amp;rsquo;s positioned between dire enemies, it&amp;rsquo;s mostly safe. The elves even call it &amp;ldquo;The Nail&amp;rdquo; swearing it holds everything together. Maybe so, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean it doesn&amp;rsquo;t need help. There are lots of jobs for adventurers here. Balster &amp;ndash; that guy with the little silver drill on his belt? He even knows your name. He wants you to kill the Great Dragons. Maudline wants to double cross the party in a scheme with the Barbarians and the Magistrate wants some nasties stirred up to the top. So choose your poison. But a thing you should know &amp;ndash; Iron Wall is a double city. Down below is something that&amp;rsquo;s not just an archeological dig. Ugly things live down there and they use powerful, ancient relics for weapons. #114 is not for the timid - it&amp;rsquo;s for you.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #114" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>