<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165364">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/PWVFDaB_taUph2nh9rcaxGOwgOY=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230340.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/v_QrgNldxVL1YB42lHzxHtd1xb0=/0x0/pic2230340.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Old Bridge" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It was on his birthday that Gotrain dreamed and saw the prognostication of his death. His witch soothed him &amp;ldquo;No worries,&amp;rdquo; she lied. But she had seen death too in the bones of halfling children and the livers of squalling cats. It didn&amp;rsquo;t matter that Gotrain depended on her. The Storms had chosen her to get him to the Black Flame Bridge and manipulate events to the will of the Godslayer. That&amp;rsquo;s the set up. The party is lining up - banding together to play out strange, new rhythms in history.  You get to save Gotrain with the spy from the musical society, or kill him off in the service of the thief queen of the Umbra.  How about you? Can you see the end of the Black Flame Bridge? Does it hang in space for you or go on forever? Whichever -watch your step. You&amp;rsquo;re the next act.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #115" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>