<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165322">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/MLHoA1xl9AyUMjW5Ve6m1nonkok=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230084.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/BuK6lj1YDr0ga7rJnjvmtM19RRw=/0x0/pic2230084.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Traveling Show" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Broldsen met Stanly when they performed years ago at the Dreck and Bother. What a disaster! But later they met to commiserate and hit it off. Now they&amp;rsquo;re running a super successful theatre troupe and having fun. The start-up was rough and they had to practice some ancillary skills for the first few years - like pick-pocketing, spy craft and information trade support. They&amp;rsquo;re prosperous now, but why give all that up? The Musical Society has asked for help keeping the Horn of Doom out of the hands of the Demon King and Broldsen and Stanly et al have all the skills to do it. They&amp;rsquo;ll save the world and keep up old skills at the same time. There&amp;rsquo;s a place for you here, too. If you can strut, if you can charm &amp;ndash; plus hide some covert skill &amp;ndash; show &amp;lsquo;em your stuff. Broldsen and Stanly need you.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #090" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="59138" value="Rodney Ruppert, II" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>