<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165375">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/L2VJ4VX-XAL45i__roJOovD4dKE=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230373.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/vJS5QrT-IOHepoTYl3FUDD8NnjE=/0x0/pic2230373.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Sky Prison" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Execution isn&amp;rsquo;t an option in the Commonwealth. As a work around, the nation suspends really bad guys - dangles them down below Sky City. They think this method is foolproof. But, really? Not so much. Nobody can lock up the truth, so when they suspend a traitorous priest, they find his ideas have wings. His body, though still needs rescuing. You could do it. You&amp;rsquo;ve got a pretty good chance of busting him out thanks to the Dragon Writ Armor he wears that lets him foil the powers of evil.  So get your papers in order and head to Sky City. Just be warned &amp;ndash; Sky Prison is a hive of racism. Gendra, a winged guard loathes humans. All humans. Theragain, ditto for elves. So factor that in. Then update yourself on what the ice elemental and the God King are scheming before you plot and strike.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #125" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="71927" value="Christopher Cortright" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>