<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165360">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/_l-yDPxuZBH8uQKm7GvRf6gtG9o=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230346.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/7PdE7BbIo0mu3746XLFr8fiL2io=/0x0/pic2230346.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Kobolds&#039; Temple" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A long time ago the Great Dragons won the War of Corruption. Temples were erected to their memory to keep them remembered. Then they rested. But memories fade. Now the Third Age is emerging, the Dragons are waking. They&amp;rsquo;re talking to a little kobold - Gyr&amp;rsquo;s his name - and he lives in one of their dragon temples. But what can Gyr do? He&amp;rsquo;s got no cred. Fortunately there&amp;rsquo;s a scruffy scholar living in the temple. He passes as a god, but knows his dragons. A barbarian warrior princess is scouting the temple too. She wants the totems back the kobolds steal from her borders. Then there&amp;rsquo;s a stash of scholar bones awaiting burial. Yes. More than a few interest groups here, looking to hire adventurers. Dragon translators are needed and some muscle behind them. Sign up or make your mark for the Dragons. They&amp;rsquo;re the good guys.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #111" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>