<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165399">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/HamRLE46u7WFh56xwHCEcKvQ2Fo=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230716.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/4iOyM2fAA5z18nVabv0QHd7OzpY=/0x0/pic2230716.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Lighting Waste" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Godslayer got banished to Pirate Island when he killed a god, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean he can&amp;rsquo;t see all futures and just about everything else as well. But there is one place the Godslayer can&amp;rsquo;t see &amp;ndash; just one. That&amp;rsquo;s the Lightning Waste where the Thunderbird sits on a nest of lightning bolts shooting down corruption. That rankled the Godslayer so he instigated false prophecy rumors to bring war to the tree where the great bird sits protecting its eggs. The Godslayer wants the tree destroyed. The Thunderbird needs to be protected. So do her eggs. Adventurers are signing up and taking body parts the Thunderbird has shed for protection. Talons and feathers and gastroliths all have powers. This battle is a fight to keep corruption at bay, so do your bit and save the Thunderbird. Just beware &amp;ndash; stay in the circle of time that the Godslayer can&amp;rsquo;t see.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #133" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>