<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165365">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/UZpvKei9kYeMMZEi-WFsIQoSUNQ=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230337.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/ibOWeq-ihwAbO86omIURZfQfKhc=/0x0/pic2230337.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Executioner&#039;s Square" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The executioner&amp;rsquo;s mask is black and looks like flame. There&amp;rsquo;s not even an eye hole, so you&amp;rsquo;ll never glimpse the guy behind it. Attendance at executions is compulsory and more ominous still? You&amp;rsquo;ll feel whatever the condemned feels &amp;ndash; the bite of the ax, the fear, the helplessness. Now it&amp;rsquo;s Meldonia&amp;rsquo;s turn to die. She got ripped into slavery very young &amp;ndash; though not as young as she looked. Powered up with adolescent defiance, she transformed herself into a rebel leader. Now her head is on the block. But wait &amp;ndash; looks like you&amp;rsquo;ll have to grab her from under the ax itself. So this is the plan: get some walk-away stones, teleport the whole party to a predestined destination that will be a mystery until you get there. But what&amp;rsquo;s to lose? No place is worse than Executioner&amp;rsquo;s Square, so rescue the green-eyed rebel. Iron Wall? That&amp;rsquo;s her destination of choice.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #116" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="71927" value="Christopher Cortright" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>