<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165402">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/_5FS-NcvzUweVcn4CvB59qowhC8=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230714.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/hbSx7cpAnNbKcBLJl_XRQKJwSoQ=/0x0/pic2230714.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Secrets of Renegade Archetypes II" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="2791" value="Pathfinder System Compatible Product" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#10;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;&amp;#9;Even More New Archetypes for 3rd Party Publisher Classes&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Secrets for Renegade Archetypes II gives you - yes, you guessed it - even more new archetypes for the most popular base classes created by your favorite 3rd Party Publishers allowing you to make the most out of the most radical and revolutionary designs available for the Pathfinder Rolplaying Game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The classes (and their archetypes) supported by this product are as follows:  &amp;#10;&amp;#10;     Death Knight (Rogue Genius Games):  Death Paramours use their bond with the Low Road to steal the souls of their departing victims before they have a chance to face final judgment, and raise their undead bodies as servants and temporary vessels for their own soul.&amp;#10;     Elven Archer (Kobold Press): Elven Exemplars blend natural and arcane magic with master archery, representing the apex of elven civilization's finest aspects. Their arrows of pure energy, scroll arrows, ranged spellstrikes and versatile spell list makes them deadly opponents and allies.&amp;#10;     Machinesmith and Fleshwraith (Louis Porter Jr. Design):  Cybernetics Doctors are scientists bordering the edge of sanity, experimenting with invasive grafts and devices like brains in jars and other improvements intended to reinforce one's physical capabilities, whether with glass and metal or flesh and bone.&amp;#10;     Pact Magic Binder (Radiant House): The Artisan and Lover are two new constellations that all binders can attempt to tap upon in order to create incredible pieces of craftsmanship, or promote peace, affection and understanding. Each comes with a new spirit to bind.&amp;#10;     Shadow Assassin (Rogue Genius Games): Mage Slayers forsake their deadly strikes in order to resist spells, hit through magic protections, and break the concentration of spellcasters. They may track their victims over long distances, proving immunity to fear is always a handy gift.&amp;#10;     Swordmaster (Dread Fox Games): Braggarts have a great natural skill with both their chosen weapon and their tongue. Passionate about their personal quest, they act recklessly in combat with unique maneuvers in order to provoke and punish their foes, swashbuckling their way to success.&amp;#10;     Witch Hunter (Rogue Genius Games): Witch Eaters have a taste for magic, especially the living kind. Their ability to leech spells and consume body parts of their fallen victims in order to receive their courage, insight or strength make them as feared as could be a werewolf in some communities.&amp;#10;     Wolf Shifter (Paizo Fans United): The Werebeast includes 13 animal variants to the wolf for all those who wish to play a serpentine, mastodon, tiger... or yes, a tyrannosaur-themed lycanthrope/barbarian.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="14590" value="The Secrets of" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="10662" value="Rite Publishing" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="65213" value="Charles Carrier" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="22956" value="Jean-Philipe Chapleau" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="24651" value="John E. Ling, Jr." />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="52310" value="Nicholas Milasich" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="22014" value="Jonathan Palmer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="13406" value="Louis Porter, Jr." />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="58873" value="Benjamin Rombeaut" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="12997" value="Owen K.C. Stephens" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77812" value="Accuracy0" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77813" value="Karla Frazetty" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="74351" value="Felipe Pesantez" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="73769" value="Michael Richards" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="69513" value="Fadly Romdhani" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77814" value="Boris Scorcos" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77288" value="Elizabeth Steyn" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77811" value="Lachy Wyatt" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="77815" value="Mursku Xenos" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="32158" value="Kevin H. Yancey" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="29416" value="Steven D. Russell" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>