<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="165446">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Heli Heroes" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>It all started, not with a bang, but with a whimper&amp;hellip;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Times are good. The Soviet Union has crumbled and the old enemies are long gone. Regions and states that were such flashpoints, like Libya, the Middle East and Africa are quieter than at perhaps any time in their histories. It hardly makes sense to maintain a large standing army anymore. So, responding to popular demand, politicians began reducing military expenditure and started automating their defenses. In order to keep dictators and terrorists from taking advantage of the situation, all tactical planning in each region has been given over to a computer. The system has direct command and control over the remaining troops and automatically controlled weaponry such as missile silos. Potential conflicts can also be solved by the computer alone. A total of 29 such systems were installed over a time. For many years, things could hardly have worked smoother. But in the rush to utilize new media, the Internet grew dramatically, bringing the world ever closer together, and becoming so complex in the process that nobody had an overview any longer.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Heli Heroes updates the old-school &amp;quot;shoot &amp;acute;em up&amp;quot; arcade machine games to new dimensions on today's PCs. Developed by Reality Pump Studios (Earth 2150, World War III: Black Gold) the console style title is designed for both PC and X-box platform. The PC version shows the latest possibilities in fast action graphics and arcade games. The player commands an AH-64 Apache Longbow or a Russian Hokum helicopter. The goal is to fly through various levels and carry out the mission objectives. During the mission the player will find on the map, different types of weapons and additional offensive and defensive systems. The look and feel of the game is a 3-dimensional landscape that the player flies his helicopter over, through and into.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Game Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2147" value="Action" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2505" value="Shoot 'em Up" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2514" value="Flight" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2508" value="Military" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2317" value="War - Modern" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2422" value="Local Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="2" />
						               				<releasedate value="2002-01-30" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="13534" value="Reality Pump Studios" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="13544" value="TopWare Interactive" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="5" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>