<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165400">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/fO3G5W8Ek_fs_KHnRm422gkkH2E=/fit-in/200x150/pic2230715.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/Om_h8bzMDVBBoyCPW-X7M-y9OV0=/0x0/pic2230715.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Grand Gardens" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Grand Gardens were built as a place where the elves could remember who they are. But recently protesters demanding the integration of elven society with the other races have overrun the gardens. The Master Gardener sides with the protestors, but everything about the whole situation worries the senators. Just recently a protestor self-immolated in the Twilight Garden and now his fiery specter is inflaming protestors. It also might be true that an earlier Master Gardener messed around with Daashiono stock and secrets in the past, so beware unidentifiable creatures coming to fruition, inhabiting the interior of manmade cliffs and mountains. Proceed carefully. Plants in the garden make seeds that hold all the knowledge in the elven archives. They need to be protected &amp;ndash; so does the fruit of the dragon birch trees. Take some of that with you. It will sustain you for thirty days.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Toys for the Sandbox is not a module, it is not a campaign setting, instead it is a framework for GMs to use to reinforce their own imaginations. Sometimes players zig when you expect them to zag, other times they take your plot point into a back alley and leave it penniless and bleeding. Each week we present a new location with a map and some flavor text. In addition we add 4 NPCs with a bit of history and a few simple thoughts on how to stat them for whatever game you are playing. There are also 6 plot hooks each with 3 ways to twist them. Added to that there is usually a table or two filled with rumors and encounters.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="17791" value="Toys for the Sandbox" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Toys for the Sandbox #132" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="22105" value="Occult Moon" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="49133" value="Shane Knysh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="59137" value="Quinn Conklin" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>