<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165665">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="3" value="A Barbárkirály" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="10026" value="Kard és Mágia" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>user summary&amp;#10;&amp;#10;From the English version published in Fight On! #11:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Beyond the border city of Velft, where the legion of General Jos&amp;eacute; Antonio Balaz&amp;aacute;n upholds the law, the great eastern trading route leaves civilisation behind. After the ploughed fields of the townlands and the small villages and guard towers of the valleys stand only endless mountain ranges, cold and unforgiving. These harsh wastes were once the domain of the Barbarian King, whose men bowed before animalistic spirits and fought with weapons of brass. Their merciless raids left all who opposed them dead or enslaved. So it was until the death of their King, after which men in mail came from the plains, showing the barbarians as little pity as they had been shown under the King&amp;rsquo;s reign.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Today the fortress-city of Castle Evening stands on the lands where the barbarians roamed, and barges plow their once-holy lake. The initial conquerors, the knighthoods of Alliria and Mitra, were eventually defeated by the fanatical inquisitor-priests of Talorn, shamefully exiled from the land of their hard-won victory. The abundant mines and rich pastures have since transformed these far vales into something else, a place of order and watchful sentries. Yet beyond Castle Evening, the peaks stand silent as ever. And it is said that, in a valley haunted by the shades of savage warriors, there is yet to be uncovered the burial place of their last warlord: the Barbarian King.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2011" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="156" value="Fantasy (Low Fantasy)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="1013" value="Fantasy (Sword &amp; Sorcery)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="4" value="(Self-Published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="20611" value="Gábor Lux" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="20611" value="Gábor Lux" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="20611" value="Gábor Lux" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>