<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="165608">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="2014 FIFA World Cup Brazil" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>2014 FIFA World Cup Brazil is the official video game for the 2014 FIFA World Cup, published by EA Sports for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360. It was released on April 15, 2014 in North America, April 17 in Europe and Australia, and April 24 in Brazil and Japan, as was the case with the 2010 edition.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Gameplay improvements from FIFA 14 include dribbling, an increased accuracy in passing and first-touch mechanics.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The game's campaign mode, Road to Rio de Janeiro, allows players to play through qualification and the actual FIFA World Cup. For only the second time in the history of World Cup video games the entire qualification series will be playable. The 2010 version only presented the UEFA and CONMEBOL groups in their true to life form. Another mode, Road to Rio de Janeiro, will allow players to compete in an online tournament across the 12 venues of the 2014 FIFA World Cup. It is similar in format to Seasons in FIFA 14 and Expedition mode from UEFA Euro 2012.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Captain Your Country, Online FIFA World Cup, Story of Qualifying, and Story of the Finals modes (the latter two integrated with EA Sports Football Club) from the 2010 edition return.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;For the first time in the FIFA series, coaches as well as spectators, either in the stadium or through FIFA Fan Fest and generic viewing events worldwide, are included to improve the immersive feeling. Coaches and spectators will react to happenings on the pitch, from scoring a goal to getting a card and winning the World Cup.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: Wikipedia, &amp;quot;2014 FIFA World Cup Brazil (video game)&amp;quot;, available under the CC-BY-SA License.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4435" value="PlayStation 3" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4407" value="Xbox 360" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2157" value="Sports" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2373" value="Sports - Soccer" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2313" value="Cooperative" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2422" value="Local Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2310" value="Network Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="7" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-04-15" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="12297" value="EA Canada" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="12296" value="EA Sports" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="2" />
			<average value="5.65" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4407" name="xbox360" friendlyname="Xbox 360 Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="4435" name="ps3" friendlyname="PlayStation 3 Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0.65" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="6" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>