<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165668">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/uw-zm2-_tA6hkwDm8dRzysotrYI=/fit-in/200x150/pic2235603.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/dTECzJozawtjqfTMbiWmo96nOxI=/0x0/pic2235603.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Adventure in a Con: Legend of the One-Toes" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="3251" value="Aether" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Adventure in a Con:  an adventure designed with the &amp;AElig;ther Random Setting Generator, run Friday night of a convention, written on Saturday of the convention, and illustrated by an artist who attended the convention.  It&amp;rsquo;s an entire adventure pulling talent from a convention!  It&amp;rsquo;s an Adventure in a Con!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Legend of the One-Toes&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The PCs are a group of cavemen and women who are the last remnants of their tribe.  Last night there was a loud bang and a bright flash which knocked all of the PCs out after hearing their Shaman raise an alarm. Now it's several hours later, the Shaman is gone, and the PCs find odd footprints leading away from the cave that seem to have only one toe, and a skin pattern that they have never seen before.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Things only get weirder as the PCs follow the tracks and find a mysterious egg-shaped cave standing on four shiny metal trees...&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This adventure was designed by using the Random Setting Generator included in the &amp;AElig;ther Core Book and was designed at Gamicon Chi in Iowa City, Iowa on March 8th of 2013.  The players rolled the various aspects of three settings and chose their favorite from those results.  This adventure was based entirely on their rolls:  a Stone Age setting with a Near Future level of technology that was an Epic Fantasy setting.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This resulting adventure was crafted through their actions, written during the convention by Kevin Rohan and illustrated by special guest artist, Tyler Walpole.  It is designed for three to six players, and, true to its roots, is perfect for either a convention game, a one-shot game, or possibly even a springboard into a larger campaign!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="175" value="History (Prehistoric)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="183" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2090" value="Dice (Percentile)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="11526" value="Silver Gryphon Games" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="34851" value="Kevin Rohan" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="11990" value="Tyler Walpole" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="34851" value="Kevin Rohan" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>