<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="165790">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Fatal Theory" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>When Nick Mayhem gets wind of zombies walking the streets, he doesn't just sit around waiting for the worst to happen. Hell no, he picks up a baseball bat and takes the carnage head on! Soon he finds himself tangled in a plot involving demons, a talking sword, a whole army of possessed soldiers and one total babe of a sniper -- can Nick Mayhem save his city from destruction? Will he find love in a city mid-apocalypse?!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;With an engine built from the ground up by two brothers and fighting game fans, this game borrows the best from the fighting genre and beat'em ups and mashes them together. The result is fluid controls, insane aerial juggling and devastating special attacks to let you wreck your way through hordes of enemies at a time!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;     All about fluid controls and wicked combos -- the bigger your combo, the higher your damage multiplier!&amp;#10;     Power up! Find new weapons, level them up to unlock devastating new special attacks, and pump up Nick's stats at the shop.&amp;#10;     Bizarre story, told in cool comic book style.&amp;#10;     Local multiplayer: co-op in arcade mode or duke it out in versus, with gamepad support for 1-2 controllers.&amp;#10;     Arcade and Survival modes, both single player and local co-op ready.&amp;#10;     Made for modding: literally everything in the game can be reskinned!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Developer Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2342" value="Beat 'em Up" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2148" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2659" value="Zombies" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2313" value="Cooperative" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2422" value="Local Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="2" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-04-02" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="28098" value="2 Hit Studio" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="28098" value="2 Hit Studio" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>