<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="165848">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/AT8Goci2nZ646BZyF-UHSRDX4kw=/fit-in/200x150/pic4643837.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/GgCtBkuJcwx8vPPwLz2jr49nMNE=/0x0/pic4643837.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Organizations, Agencies and Secret Societies" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="305" value="d20 Modern" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This supplement contains descriptions of nearly 50 unique agencies, organizations, and secret societies from the early 20th century. Although they are designed for use with the 1948 Campaign Setting, they can also be used seamlessly with any WWII campaign setting, such as Hell on Earth (1939-1945). They can also be used with any other sort of RPG dealing with the early 20th century including World War I, 1930s gangsters, Lovecraftian horror, or archaeological adventure. These organizations can also be used with non-d20 rules systems, as they are merely descriptions of organizations. Aside from being classified as ?Allegiances? under the d20 rule system, they do not actually use game mechanics.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This supplement is divided into three sections. The first deals with government agencies including the Nazi Occult Bureau, the British MI-5, the Department of Psychotronic Research, and the GRU, among others. These semi-secret government agencies are outlined with a discussion on their purposes, policies, and practices. The Second section of this supplement focuses on secret societies, many of which deal with occultism, divine faith, or organized crime. These include the Templar Knights, the Rosicrucians, the Priory of Sion, the League of Blood, the Vril, the Genovese crime family, Skull and Bones, the Black Dragon Society, the Golden Dawn, the New Forest Witches, and many more. The descriptions also feature brief stat-blocks that detail when the society was founded, the regions of the world it is active in, its symbol, and its mission. The last section of this supplement discusses political and social ideologies of the early 20th century such as Communism, Nazism, and Capitalism, as well as a few resistance groups such as the White Russians. Each description includes an overview of the group's purpose, goals and membership.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Buy this supplement today and add a new level of intrigue and mysticism to your early 20th century RPG!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2004" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="167" value="History (Alternative)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="951" value="Occult" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="953" value="War" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgsetting" id="4052" value="1948" />
		
									
			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2138" value="Progression Tree (Skills, professions, magic abilities, etc.)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="10181" value="Bloodstone Press" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="16530" value="John Alger" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="16530" value="John Alger" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="27696" value="Butch Mapa" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="22596" value="Tony Perna" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="22064" value="Shawn Richter" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="15037" value="Jason Walton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="16530" value="John Alger" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="21655" value="Chris Cant" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>