<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="165811">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="NASCAR The Game: 2013" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>Drivers, Start Your Engines!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;NASCAR The Game 2013 is the 1st title in the series available on Steam and PC, featuring all the official drivers, teams and tracks from the official NASCAR Sprint Cup Series Championship. Delve into the most authentic NASCAR experience with eye-opening graphics, competitive AI and the most robust multiplayer support system yet. Work towards the ultimate prize, being crowned the Sprint Cup Series Champion and for the first time, experience the intense, thrilling action from behind the wheel of a Gen 6 model stock car.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Relive and rewrite iconic moments from recent NASCAR history with Inside Line Highlights, recreated using real-world telemetry data from seasons 2011, 2012 and 2013, allowing players to experience the heat of the moment in one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most exciting motorsports. And, for the 1st time in sports games, NASCAR The Game 2013 will release further update packs as the climax to the season unfolds.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Key Features:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Battle your way to the top of the official NASCAR Sprint Cup Series against competitive and aggressive AI&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Stunning visuals and handling deliver the most authentic NASCAR experience ever&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Design and race your own Gen 6 car model with an all-new and sophisticated paint booth toolkit&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Relive and Rewrite iconic moments from recent NASCAR history include the 2013 season as it happens!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Immerse yourself in full race weekends, including practice, qualifying and race sessions&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Challenge or race as all 43 official NASCAR drivers, on all of the official 2013 tracks&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Relive and rewrite NASCAR history with additional Inside Line Highlights packages&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Developer Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;NASCAR The Game: 2013 features the Gen-6 cars from the 2013 Sprint Cup Series season including an updated 2013 season roster of drivers. The Windows game includes online multi-player as well as AI competition.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: Wikipedia, &amp;quot;NASCAR The Game: Inside Line&amp;quot;, available under the CC-BY-SA License.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2154" value="Racing" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2456" value="Driving" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2310" value="Network Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="0" />
						               				<releasedate value="2013-06-21" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="13106" value="Eutechnyx" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="13106" value="Eutechnyx" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="1" />
			<average value="5" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>