<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166096">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/Ci-kN-pQ1-pJj2Ku29A_8E3X0g8=/fit-in/200x150/pic2243903.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/XkFAoYLmJJapzrNDdsRStJR551k=/0x0/pic2243903.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Nova Praxis: Savage Worlds Edition" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="286" value="Savage Worlds" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Things have changed. We have changed.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Earth is lost to us, but even in the aftermath of this terrible tragedy, we grow, evolve, and even prosper. We have witnessed the death of our mother and the birth of a new era.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In what might have been the end, salvation was found in the synthesis of biology and technology. Augmentation, ranging from basic genetic manipulation to Apotheosis, set us on the path of prosperity. And more, these advances reinforced the importance of identity, individuality, and what it means to be human.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The loss of Earth and the resulting Exodus gave us an opportunity to start over with a clean slate. And we seized it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The need for organization, stability, and a reliable government was clear, but the old ways came to be viewed by the survivors as archaic, clumsy, and too easily corrupted.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It was time for a new way&amp;hellip;a Nova Praxis.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Today, social networks allow the will of the people to be measured instantly, accurately, and without the need for representation. The Coalition, guided by the collective voice of its people, has established new homes on worlds lit by new suns. Molecular assembly technology has made it possible for society to provide a quality of life never before imagined, at essentially no cost, to everyone. And we are virtually immortal.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;But can this would-be utopia last?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Corruption in the Coalition government fosters decay from within. The Houses, our benefactors and patrons, run shadowy networks of intrigue, espionage, and assassination. Apostates, those who refuse citizenship in the Coalition, condemn those who would trade their privacy for the Coalition&amp;rsquo;s security. Remnants of Earth&amp;rsquo;s old governments wage a guerilla war on Coalition forces. Ideological extremists commit acts of terror using the latest horror to spring from a factory or test tube&amp;hellip;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;And the value of a human soul is weighed and measured in lines of code.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Nova Praxis is a post-singularity sci-fi setting that explores transhumanism and post-scarcity societies against a backdrop of action, adventure, conspiracy, and intrigue.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Nova Praxis is&amp;hellip;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;hellip;a tabletop role-playing game featuring the Savage Worlds Role-Playing Game System, tailored specifically for Nova Praxis.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;hellip;compatible with, but does not require, the Savage Worlds Science Fiction Companion.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;hellip;a relatively &amp;ldquo;hard sci-fi&amp;rdquo; setting that takes place during the aftermath of a short-lived technological singularity.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;hellip;an exploration of the tropes of transhuman sci-fi: mind uploading, resleeving, artificial intelligence, and augmentation.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;hellip;an exploration of the societal impacts of a reputation-based post-scarcity economy.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;hellip;a game in which players play characters who slip between the cracks of civilization and perform jobs their patrons would rather keep off the books.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;...a setting full of conflict. The Houses wage a secret Shadow War against each other, purist and transhuman ideologies clash violently, and apostates rebel against the oppression of the Coalition government.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;...home to railguns, powered armor, starships, security drones, bipedal combat frames, swarms of nanomachines, kill-sats, and the horrors of accelerated evolution gone wrong.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="940" value="Action / Adventure" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="958" value="Corporations" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="954" value="Crime (Conspiracy)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="952" value="Politics / Government" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="163" value="Science Fiction (Hard Sci Fi)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgsetting" id="25845" value="Nova Praxis" />
		
									
			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2107" value="Campaign Setting (game world)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2114" value="Cards (cards drive the action)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2140" value="Dice Step (variable dice vs. static target)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2129" value="Exploding Dice (Die may 'explode' into a second roll)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2143" value="Grid-based (uses square terrain for move/combat)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2100" value="Point Based (allocate points to get skills, powers, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="14986" value="Void Star Studios" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="24013" value="Wes Brown" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="60386" value="Leland Dutro" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="18727" value="Sean Patrick Fannon" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="57327" value="Joel Knapp" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="41674" value="Mike McConnell" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="56680" value="Tomi Sarkkinen" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78004" value="Rob Stroud" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78005" value="Kyle Stroud" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78002" value="Tommy Townsley" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78003" value="Steve Townsley" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="56679" value="Andrew Chason" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="41674" value="Mike McConnell" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="37492" value="Andreas Schroth" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="43681" value="Andree Wallin" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="13964" value="Aaron Acevedo" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="41676" value="Kristan McConnell" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="41674" value="Mike McConnell" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="29161" value="Mitch Williams" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="67958" value="Joshua Yearsley" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="2" />
			<average value="5.5" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="2.5" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="15" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="1" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>