<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="166105">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Worms 3" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>The follow up to the award-winning, best-selling Worms 2: Armageddon is here! Worms 3 has been designed and developed exclusively for mobile.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Worms&amp;trade; 3 includes 27 Single Player missions, Body Count mode, asynchronous multiplayer, gorgeous new graphics, worm classes, AirPlay functionality, strategic playing cards and all new weapons such as Nora's Virus and Canned Heat!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;DEAL yourself the advantage with a new, game-changing enhancement. Turn on the card mode and alter the start and end of each turn by the playing of strategic cards.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;COLLECT in-game rewards that allow you to purchase bronze, silver and gold cards. Build your deck from 41 fiendishly designed cards!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;ENLIST your perfect battle combination as you choose your Worms from a new &amp;lsquo;Class&amp;rsquo; system - Heavy, Scientist, Scout and classic Soldier. Each has their own unique skill and ability. Which will fit in with your style of play?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;SHOW OFF your skills by earning Achievements! A delightful blend of both the simple and complex, these goals have been deliberately engineered to push you and your Wormy skills to the limits!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;PLAY online with Asynchronous multiplayer warfare. Enroll in ranked or friendly matches and show off your prowess. Remember, with async you don&amp;rsquo;t have to commit to a full session at a time. Take your turn then go beat your friends score in the single-player Bodycount mode!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;BATTLE in multiplayer Forts or Deathmatch modes and challenge yourself with the increasingly difficult Bodycount single-player game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;CONQUER 27 single-player missions across 4 new themes (Beach, spooky, farmyard and sewer).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;CUSTOMIZE your squad and make them unique with a huge amount of customizable elements new to iOS!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;INCOMING! All your old favorite weapons plus six new ones on iOS, including a couple of returning classics such as the Old Lady and the Homing Pigeon!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;BE THE BEST and Worm your way to the top of the Leaderboards across all major game modes including single player as well as asynchronous online ranked matches.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;GREATER CONTROL for players who can now choose between an all-new D-Pad control system and the original touch controls.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;MARVEL at the glorious streamlined menu system. Gamers can now enjoy a much more pleasant and navigable menu system with a quick access player HUB for all updates and information!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;GO LARGE with the fabulous Airplay feature. Link up to Apple TV and play one one device with up to four players on the big screen. The active player can plot their move secretly on the iOS device while the waiting gamers can witness the move on the TV screen!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Developer Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="6063" value="Android" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="6826" value="iPad" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4443" value="iPhone" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4729" value="Macintosh" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2147" value="Action" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2158" value="Strategy" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2471" value="Animals" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2509" value="Comedy" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2508" value="Military" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamefranchise" id="6353" value="Worms" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameseries" id="5045" value="Worms" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2410" value="Asynchronous Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="4" />
						               				<releasedate value="2013-08-08" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="12229" value="Team17 Software Ltd." />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="12229" value="Team17 Software Ltd." />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="2" />
			<average value="6.25" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4443" name="iphone" friendlyname="iPhone Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="4729" name="macintosh" friendlyname="Macintosh Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="6063" name="android" friendlyname="Android Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="6826" name="ipad" friendlyname="iPad Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0.25" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="4" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="1" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>