<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166218">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/z88k8wEARtqy2tAj6zkq9mIlCcU=/fit-in/200x150/pic2245690.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/4f3ma3oY10d_xVTQFRF2dXZ49qU=/0x0/pic2245690.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Lostwere Forest" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A printable rpg battlemap compatible with any RPG/Dungeon-Crawl or skirmish game. Use as a standalone gameboard, or combine with any same-scale tileset. The map is 50x50, equivalen to 25 of our standard 10x10 tiles.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Contents: A forest map, with various sized muddy tracks and trails. Dense areas of forest and woods, with small clearings and rocky outcrops. A small stream winds through the forest before splitting, and is crossed in two places by small muddy fords. Animal footprints, piles of bones and mushrooms provide ambience and story hooks.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Uses: A deep forest inhabited by goblins, an ancient wood your adventurers need to get through before nightfall, the hideout of a group of werewolves that have been terrorising a nearby village, the site of an ambush, the wilderness beyond the mountains.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Download includes:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;     250dpi A4 pdf, with gridded map spread across 50 ages for easy printing.&amp;#10;     250dpi full jpeg versions (gridded and non-gridded), for VTT or poster printing.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A note on VTT use - we have deliberately kept the quality of the file high, and you may need to resize the jpeg for use in your VTT software. Keeping the file size and resolution high gives you the flexibility to use the map how you want - crop out a particular section or use the entire map, the choice is yours.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="26436" value="Heroic Maps Giant Maps" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Heroic Maps Giant Maps" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="26500" value="Heroic Maps" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="72892" value="J. Bilton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="72892" value="J. Bilton" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="72892" value="J. Bilton" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>