<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="166220">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Class of Heroes 2" />
			
						                               				
				<name type="alternate" sortindex="1" value="Ken to Mahō to Gakuenmono Tsū" />
			    				
				<name type="alternate" sortindex="1" value="剣と魔法と学園モノ。2" />
			
						               													<description>Class of Heroes 2 (&amp;#229;&amp;#137;&amp;#163;&amp;#227;&amp;#129;&amp;#168;&amp;#233;&amp;#173;&amp;#148;&amp;#230;&amp;#179;&amp;#149;&amp;#227;&amp;#129;&amp;#168;&amp;#229;&amp;#173;&amp;#166;&amp;#229;&amp;#156;&amp;#146;&amp;#227;&amp;#131;&amp;#162;&amp;#227;&amp;#131;&amp;#142;&amp;#227;&amp;#128;&amp;#130;2 Ken to Mah&amp;#197;&amp;#141; to Gakuenmono Ts&amp;#197;&amp;#171;) is the sequel to Class of Heroes released in Japan on June 24, 2009 and includes more jobs and majors for the characters. Recently, a Kickstarter project was initiated by MonkeyPaw Games and Gaijinworks to fund the localization and the production of the sequel's limited edition. Although the project did not fund, MonkeyPaw and Gaijinworks promised to continue the translation and release the game digitally with the game set to be released on PSN in mid 2013, and have started a signup to gauge interest on a possible limited physical release, which would also include a code to obtain the game digitally. The campaign proved successful, with 2700 signing up and even more people pre-ordering the game when the pre-sale started. About 200 physical copies were made available through the Canadian online shop Video Games Plus, the rest of the production run being exclusive to those who had pre-ordered via the Gaijinworks website until May 12, 2013. The copies sold at VGP are limited to one copy per customer and also do not come with download codes for digital copies. Also, fans could vote for the cover artwork used for the physical release, with people who had backed the unsuccessful Kickstarter campaign getting a special cover different from that of the copies pre-ordered on the website. The physical release had to be delayed when players of the digital version that was released on June 4, 2013 reported several bugs. The bugs were later fixed in an update to the digital version on October 15, 2013 and the UMD release started shipping in the same month. It was the last PSP game released in North America to get a physical release.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: Wikipedia, &amp;quot;Class of Heroes&amp;quot;, available under the CC-BY-SA License.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4432" value="PSP" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2155" value="RPG" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2337" value="Cute Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameseries" id="28145" value="Class of Heroes" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="1" />
						               				<releasedate value="2009-06-25" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="16621" value="ZeroDiv" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="13142" value="Acquire" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="22851" value="MonkeyPaw Games" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="2" />
			<average value="6.25" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4432" name="psp" friendlyname="PSP Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0.75" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="1" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>