<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="166224">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Bomb The Monsters!" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>Bomb the Monsters!&amp;quot; features the story of a highly talented painter who is living a perfect life with his beloved wife. But one day things are changing when a huge horde of ugly monsters invade planet earth, capture the painter's wife, and exhaust and exploit the whole planet. Now it's up to the player to stop this horrible invasion and rescue the poor hostage - easier said than done!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The very well-known gameplay offers an easy entry into the game: In every level the player needs to place a limited amount of bombs next to the monsters for getting surroundings and buildings collapse on them to drive the monsters out. But the monsters are coming in various sizes and shapes and are fat, imbecile and extremely sticky. Because of the physical structure of their bodies, these stupid creatures stick to almost everything what makes it sometimes tricky to bomb them away.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;quot;Bomb the Monsters!&amp;quot; offers over 60 levels in beautiful HD graphics; each level comes with non-linear solutions to eliminate the ugly monsters. Great music and sounds plus a motivating achievement system are part of this addictive mobile game as well and offering fun for the whole family.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Highlights:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;bull; Well known gameplay offering an easy access to the game&amp;#10;&amp;bull; Realistic physics engine and beautiful HD graphics&amp;#10;&amp;bull; Motivating achievement system with a variety of unlockable items. &amp;#10;&amp;bull; Non-linear solutions for each and every levels &amp;#10;&amp;bull; 2 worlds and 20 great levels in the FREE version! Buy the PREMIUM Version and get 40 more levels plus 4 additional and exciting new worlds! &amp;#10;&amp;bull; Great music and awesome sound effects&amp;#10;&amp;bull; Easy control&amp;#10;&amp;bull; Multilingual version (English, German, French, Italian, Spanish, Russian, Hindi, Thai, Indonesian)&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Publisher Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="6063" value="Android" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="6826" value="iPad" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4443" value="iPhone" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2165" value="Puzzle" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2337" value="Cute Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="1" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-05-30" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="28162" value="Kadus Virtual Development (Final Boss)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="27279" value="Immanitas Entertainment" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4443" name="iphone" friendlyname="iPhone Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="6063" name="android" friendlyname="Android Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="6826" name="ipad" friendlyname="iPad Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>