<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166377">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/BK3L5nlgln36c_vvnHGp6F9KTBg=/fit-in/200x150/pic2248607.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/F_FgmwPEfiJrsl1Xsv8YZvk8sMk=/0x0/pic2248607.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Japanese Vehicles of the Second World War" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="499" value="Traveller (Mongoose)" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The dominant force in the Pacific in during the middle stages of the war, the Japanese military played a desperate gamble to knock out its American and European enemies before the full weight of their retaliation could be brought to bear. Spearheaded by sea and air power, the vehicles presented in this book were used on the islands of the Pacific as the war leapt from one to another. Though not facing the massive armoured conflicts of Europe and Africa, the vehicles the Japanese employed during the war were nevertheless interesting and varied.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This supplement for Traveller introduces many vehicles that formed the fighting arm of Japan in the Second World War, and provides full details of each, allowing them to be used within games. The weapons unique to Japan are also covered, along with enough information for you to use them in your own games and own vehicle designs.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Uses in Traveller&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The vehicles found in this book could potentially form the basis of a campaign set in the Second World War. They may also be of interest to those who are simply curious as to how real-world vehicles can be implemented using the Traveller vehicle design system. However, we suspect many more players will want to actually use them in their games, even on planets far in the future and hundreds of light years away!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;We have provided game mechanics for many vehicles, from the devastatingly agile Mitsubishi Zero, to the Type 95 tank but, at the end of the day, a Type 95 need not look like a Type 95 if it were built to these specifications on an alien world. It could end up looking very different but have the same characteristics listed in this book. By this token, what this book provides is a solid set of military vehicles available at Tech Level 5. A referee can use them to fully flesh out a military force on a Tech Level 5 world and provide interesting variations on themes in order to give his world more depth.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;For example, a referee creating a military force for a new world may simply design a single main battle tank for it before moving on to the artillery piece, the fighter plane, and so on. With this book, he can present a military force that has a defined timeline with the development of its vehicles, so there is not just one main battle tank but several, each a replacement of the one before though with all still in service, with the very best units getting the latest generation of tank.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Players can have fun with this book as well, especially if they are engaging in paramilitary actions or running their own mercenary force. What this book will provide them is a list of Tech Level 5 vehicles that, while outmatched by more sophisticated enemies, will be perfectly serviceable (and at a cheaper price!) on more primitive worlds and will be capable of standing up against infantry from higher Tech Levels &amp;ndash; at least, until plasma weaponry and missiles become prevalent.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="278" value="Culture (Asian / Far Eastern)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="184" value="History" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="953" value="War" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25886" value="Vehicles of the Second World War" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2124" value="Lifepath Character Generation (Character starts at birth)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2100" value="Point Based (allocate points to get skills, powers, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2134" value="Random Attribute Generation (during Character Creation)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="2826" value="Mongoose Publishing" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="77651" value="Noel O'Connor" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="4207" value="Matthew Sprange" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="50279" value="Wikimedia Commons" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="4207" value="Matthew Sprange" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>