<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166406">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/_kAirbZQjS-nSj97AGRx5-rRf6c=/fit-in/200x150/pic2249023.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/wHtBBSuZdgR7pCNoeDo3-XQf6sc=/0x0/pic2249023.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Scarab: Bulk Hauler" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Scarab-class freighter is named for the squat, sturdy shape of its hull and its rugged endurance. It is just a coincidence that the original scarab is a species of &amp;ldquo;dung beetle&amp;rdquo; and this class of ship is often employed moving garbage and other unseemly cargos. The extended-hull version of the ship is known as the Kiboko-class, which is a Swahili word for hippo (a reference to its bulk and ungainly nature outside of the void). Both are cheap and dependable, though lacking in amenities. Each carries a crew of 2 to 12 and is designed to haul large quantities of everything from cargo crates, to shipping containers, to ore, trash, and even liquids like fuel or water.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The components built into these ships are about a decade behind &amp;ldquo;state of the art&amp;rdquo;. Using older designs and refurbished parts keeps the cost down but doesn&amp;rsquo;t produce a ship worth bragging about. Where the ship gets good marks is in durability. The hull is strong and well reinforced. This is necessary in order to haul dense cargo loads but also means the ship can withstand a lot of punishment. The older systems are also easy to maintain since any problems are well known and spare parts are plentiful. Lastly, the relative cost of these ships is low. That is, after all, the point. Both the Scarab-class and the Kiboko-class are unapologetically designed to get the job done, reliably, for the minimum price possible. These common ships are not much respected by ambitious independent pilots or status-conscious smugglers, but are very popular with companies and agencies that need a large number of cheap haulers.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Scarab package contains four highly detailed, layered PDF files:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;     Main Book&amp;#10;         20page PDF file detailing the ships, interior areas, and exo-frame cargo movers.&amp;#10;         Contains several 3D rendered scenes as well as orthographic views of the ships.&amp;#10;         Includes system independent statistics designed for easy adaption to your game of choice.&amp;#10;         Background, art, and text are on different layers for custom display and printing.&amp;#10;    &amp;#10;     Map Pages&amp;#10;         21 page PDF file containing complete interior maps and instructions for assembly.&amp;#10;        Miniature-scale maps for tactical combat with an optional 1 inch = 5 ft grid.&amp;#10;        Divided into pages for easy printing in full color or printer-friendly black and white.&amp;#10;        Selectable layers include: grid, black &amp;amp; white version, optional objects, and more.&amp;#10;    &amp;#10;    2 Uncut Map Images&amp;#10;        Two single page PDF files containing giant images of the complete deckplans.&amp;#10;        The Scarab image is 24x36 inches; Kiboko 24x52.&amp;#10;        Select either a light or dark background (for printing or projection/display).&amp;#10;        Includes layers for grid, black &amp;amp; white version, optional objects, and background choice.&amp;#10;    &amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;These ships are bulk haulers and much of their interior is dedicated to a single, cavernous hold.  In a game setting the huge cargo hold could be used to store several ground vehicles or fighters instead of cargo, or could just be a great place to have a fight. The layered maps allow for the cargo to be shown or hidden &amp;ndash; meaning you can have an empty hold or one crowded with palettes, crates, and barrels.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;As always, this product is designed to give you ready-made ships to plug into your setting and rules of choice - lending depth and detail to your campaign. When it&amp;rsquo;s time to play, zero hour is ready!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="183" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25160" value="Armada Codex" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Armada Codex 01-04" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="11073" value="0 hr art &amp; technology" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="13277" value="Ryan Wolfe" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="13277" value="Ryan Wolfe" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="13277" value="Ryan Wolfe" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>