<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166698">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/1zNaCLoN39qYQXyalg-ko0dxQWE=/fit-in/200x150/pic2256625.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/ITB-DqWY8jr9VnT2ruA-QL0SiQA=/0x0/pic2256625.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Vertiginous Infiltrators of Sargosyala VII" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="1652" value="Labyrinth Lord" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Almost a thousand years ago, the overlords of the planet Xalvoria were at war with the theocratic republicans of Sargosyala VII, a rocky, metal-rich planet at the edge of the dark nebula. Due to the military superiority of the Sargosyalans, the Xalvorians could see no way to turn the tide of battle &amp;mdash; until they went looking for solutions in their own biotechnology sector.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The vat lords of the Xalvorian criminal underworld bartered the perfect weapon for their own political rehabilitation. In light of the potential spoils they could see coming from an end to the war &amp;mdash; and an end to the Sargosyalans &amp;mdash;t he overlords were more than happy to oblige. The results of this alliance tore Sargosyala VII apart from the inside out.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Grown in vats by unlawful geneticists, the vertiginous infiltrators are perfect copies of the Sargosyalan race, able to mimic the mannerisms and behaviours of anyone they could observe. They were deployed against the Sargosyalans and quickly took over key positions within that race&amp;rsquo;s leadership. Not only did they capture vital military resources for the Xalvorians, but the paranoia these double agents created within the Sargosyalan ranks was a setback they could never recover from. Within a few short decades, a war that had rages and stalled for more than a century was over, and no true Sargosyalan remained alive.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;With their homeworld and all their colonies overrun by the Xalvorian overlords, the vertiginous infiltrators are all that is left of the Sargosyalans. Undying, they continue to serve their masters, infiltrating the societies of other alien races &amp;mdash; but no subsequent success can compare to their original triumph over the beings they were made to mimic.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="183" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25930" value="Monthly Monsters" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Monthly Monster 14-07LL" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28236" value="Red Box Vancouver" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78226" value="Nathan Jones" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>