<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166765">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/IgHhj6nq6Rm1IhZwuiEfXA1Rlws=/fit-in/200x150/pic2255937.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/StaUvis8sSTgc3tT47bxmHY8oX4=/0x0/pic2255937.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Slime Wizards" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="1652" value="Labyrinth Lord" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Once upon a time, not so long ago, a small group of adventurers set out to make their fortunes. They journeyed long and hard, and braved many trials and tribulations along the way, but at last they came to the end of their journey &amp;mdash; the ancient city of Ardoussarlis. Long has it lain in ruins, and even today, none have tried to resettle its vast and crumbled palaces. But these  adventurers paid no heed to reconstruction. No, they were only after treasure! Haunted by ghosts and fell beasts, the city is, but every so often, someone ventures inside its ill-omened confines.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Unlike so many others who died horribly, or returned with only memories of slaughter, what these adventurers found in Ardoussarlis changed their lives forever &amp;mdash; for the better. Or so they would tell you &amp;mdash; many others might beg to differ. This band of dungeoneers brought ancient machines back to the surface with them, enslaved weird, unearthly creatures, and made themselves a power to be reckoned with. Now, they ride across the countryside on top of strange platforms full of gadgets and levers, often drawn by giant, wormish centipedes bearing cruel arms, though some can even fly through the air. Wherever they go, they leave a trail of slime behind the, just like a slug &amp;mdash; or the alien minions they now command.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The small cadre of adventurers who formed the founding ranks of the slime wizards has since expanded, taking on new recruits who, like them, lust inordinately after gold and treasure. Other adventurers have tried to stop them, and they have suffered the odd casualty or two, but they remain at large, wreaking havoc and destruction, plundering at will.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25930" value="Monthly Monsters" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Monthly Monster 14-05LL" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28236" value="Red Box Vancouver" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78226" value="Nathan Jones" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>