<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166744">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/lWOxVt-K21sLov0H_zdDHPw0TgM=/fit-in/200x150/pic2255962.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/vDQj5CVI-tFj3w-nQ0JBrPtku9k=/0x0/pic2255962.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Grumblesticks: Kidnapper of Dwarven Children" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="11105" value="Dungeon World" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Grumblesticks is a dark, fey creature of the high, wooded mountains. With the head and teats of a sow and the body of a stunted dwarf, she stomps through the trees wearing heavy iron boots, swinging a bloody club as she goes. She is an evil legend amongst the dwarves. They claim she stalks them in the night, kidnapping dwarven children either to eat or in order to keep them in cages and slowly use their body parts in alchemical witchery &amp;mdash; all the while feeding them the flesh of their fellow dwarves.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Elves and humans have heard little of the legend of Grumblesticks, for the dwarves are reticent to speak of her. The halflings, however, know her all too well, as she stalks their shires in the night whenever dwarves are in short supply. Such is their caution that when more unscrupulous halflings travel through the mountain woods with their valuables, they will buy a dwarven slave to take with them, just in case they encounter Grumblesticks. They know she prefers dwarves, and will be distracted long enough for the halflings to escape. More unscrupulous halflings who travel without any valuables prefer just to buy parts of dwarves instead of an entire living specimen.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Whenever dwarves hear the high-pitched squeals of wild boar in the woods, they think of the legend of Grumblesticks, snuffling about in the darkness, looking for children to kidnap. And whenever they see a trail of slime, they think of her house.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Grumblesticks often stomps around the woods in her heavy iron boots. This makes it doubly disconcerting when she hides and becomes deathly silent. She likes to terrorize her prey before taking them back to the Grumblehut, but she can also be fairly efficient when in a hurry. She wields a large, spiked club that can hit two targets each round, but they must be different. Roll for each attack separately. When she hides in the woods, she has a 4-in-6 chance of surprising enemies.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25930" value="Monthly Monsters" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Monthly Monster 13-12DW-Bonus" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2121" value="Action Table (table determines action outcomes)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2099" value="Description Based (Narrative more so than Dice)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28236" value="Red Box Vancouver" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78226" value="Nathan Jones" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>