<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="166712">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/Uwp_bpnSJFo_qfZc7JnjfIS5auk=/fit-in/200x150/pic2306472.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/rX8frBSaONyXx-_4nTjkLmFFvoA=/0x0/pic2306472.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Five Nights At Freddy&#039;s" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>Five Nights At Freddy's is a point and click survival horror Indie game created by Scott Cawthon.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;You've just began work as a night security guard for 'Freddy Fazbear's Pizza Restaurant'. However, what should be an easy graveyard shift of dunking doughnuts and drinking coffee becomes much more sinister when a message left for you by a previous employee warns you that the animatronic characters at the restaurant come to life on their own at night and roam the property! It's indicated that they are responsible for several missing person reports and possibly deaths!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In Five Nights you are kept stationary in your security office. From here you can check the security cameras, operate the two doors at either side of the office and the lights just outside them. You have to survive 5 six hour shifts (each taking about 6 minutes). The Fazbear Animatronics will only move when not being viewed, and can be kept out of the office via the doors. The downside to this is using the cameras, doors or lights drains a power meter and if it reaches 0% the power cuts and you will be unable to defend yourself. You must juggle between keeping track of the 4 animatronics as they lurk menacingly about the building, checking outside your office using the lights and slamming the doors shut to stop attacks until morning comes. Each shift gets increasingly difficult with the animatronics becoming more active and aggressive.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Its simple premise, addictive gameplay, creepy atmosphere and jump-scare tactics has earned Five Nights a strong cult following, especially on Youtube.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="6063" value="Android" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="6826" value="iPad" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4443" value="iPhone" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2158" value="Strategy" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2265" value="Horror" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameseries" id="26524" value="Five Nights At Freddy's" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="1" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-08-08" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="14029" value="(Self-Developed Video Game)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="4" value="(Self-Published)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="12" />
			<average value="5.16667" />
			<bayesaverage value="5.31482" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="6978" bayesaverage="5.31482" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4443" name="iphone" friendlyname="iPhone Rank" value="419" bayesaverage="5.0774" />
											<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="2291" bayesaverage="5.22911" />
											<rank type="family" id="6063" name="android" friendlyname="Android Rank" value="281" bayesaverage="5.02452" />
											<rank type="family" id="6826" name="ipad" friendlyname="iPad Rank" value="409" bayesaverage="5.02607" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="2.69083" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="44" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="4" />
			<numweights value="1" />
			<averageweight value="3" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>