<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="166886">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="UFC Undisputed 3" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>UFC Undisputed 3 is a mixed martial arts video game featuring Ultimate Fighting Championship properties and fighters developed by Yuke's and published by THQ. It was released February 14, 2012 in North America and February 17, 2012 in Europe for the PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360. It is a sequel to UFC Undisputed 2010, making it the third and last game to be released under THQ's 2007 agreement with the UFC. The demo was released on January 24, 2012.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;UFC Undisputed 3 has improved and added changes from its predecessor, including the following:[1][2]&amp;#10;&amp;#10;New THQ servers for online play and downloadable content. Since the closing of THQ the servers are now closed.&amp;#10;The addition of Pride Mode, with Pride rules, ring, and fighters. Pride Grand Prix has also been included, with the ability to have fights in the same night with damage moving onto the next fight. Commentary is provided by Bas Rutten and Stephen Quadros. Lenne Hardt announces the fighters in Pride.&amp;#10;A brand new submission system. New submission moves includes the standing rear naked choke, standing guillotine choke, and the flying scissor heel hook.&amp;#10;Motion capture used for fighters for more realistic movement.&amp;#10;New Stats: Footwork, Ground Grapple Top and Bottom for offense and defense.&amp;#10;Fighter entrances.&amp;#10;Two game play control options: traditional and simplified (Pro and Amateur controls).&amp;#10;Leg kick TKO's, including leg breaks from blocked kicks.&amp;#10;New KO animations. &amp;quot;Finish the Fight&amp;quot; allows you to continue punching an unconscious opponent until the referee pulls you off.&amp;#10;Damage recovery between rounds.&amp;#10;New Stamina system, where stamina can only come back up so far until you are fully rested. Cuts affect stamina and energy recovery rate.&amp;#10;Redesigned striking game emphasizing jabs, quick strikes, and combinations. Elbow spamming has been fixed, with only certain fighters having elbows in clinch range. A fighter's reach is now a big part in striking, and new feint system and takedown-intercepting knees have been added.&amp;#10;New clinch controls, including a new transition in the clinch to back control. Whip knees can be done to the body and can be blocked.&amp;#10;Stat decay removed in Career Mode, and roster fighters from the UFC and Pride can now be taken through career mode.&amp;#10;New ground positions with the cage, including using the cage to set up submissions and &amp;quot;wall walking&amp;quot; back to a standing position.&amp;#10;New options, such as Stamina Simulation mode, Competition Spec mode (removes all random elements such as flash KOs and doctor stoppages), and Stat Equalizer (equalizes all stats to 90 for both fighters).&amp;#10;Fighters are now able to sway on the ground to avoid strikes.&amp;#10;Sweeps are back from UFC 2009 Undisputed, including new ones.&amp;#10;Venues available includes MGM Grand, Mandalay Bay, The O2, Bell Centre, Palms Casino Resort, and the Red Rock Resort Spa and Casino. Madison Square Garden returns from UFC 2009 Undisputed. Pride matches are realised on Saitama Super Arena and WFA matches are realised at The Joint.&amp;#10;Mario Yamasaki, Herb Dean, Yves Lavigne, Josh Rosenthal, Dan Miragliotta and Kevin Mulhall are the referees available in the game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: Wikipedia, &amp;quot;UFC Undisputed 3&amp;quot;, available under the CC-BY-SA License.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4435" value="PlayStation 3" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4407" value="Xbox 360" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2159" value="Fighting" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2493" value="Martial Arts" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameseries" id="5670" value="UFC Undisputed" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2422" value="Local Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2310" value="Network Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="2" />
						               				<releasedate value="2012-02-14" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="11855" value="Yuke's Co. Ltd" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="1288" value="Konami" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="11789" value="THQ" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4407" name="xbox360" friendlyname="Xbox 360 Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="4435" name="ps3" friendlyname="PlayStation 3 Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="5" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="1" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>