<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166818">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/OBWG5OhyU03fcK2LaSfcNa97j6Q=/fit-in/200x150/pic2276784.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/oK7E9liAsBaubWEp877YFVrm7s4=/0x0/pic2276784.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="I shall rather go alone..." />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="25950" value="I shall rather go alone..." />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From the Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is a game about people who are stuck traveling together, their route planning and their choice to rather go alone. It is hybrid of a role-playing game and a boardgame. Boundaries blur anyways.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Gather at least three persons for playing, though you might not want to go above seven. This game is designed to comfortably fit into an evening, maybe you can squeeze even two or three games in there. How long it takes will scale with players and your collective decision-happiness.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;To play this game, you will need a large sheet of paper to draw a map on, a few pencils and both a red and blue pen, as well as a deck of index cards. If you take the number of players, multiply it by 13 and then add 7, take that many index cards and you should have enough for most games.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Each of you will take on the role of a person that is stranded in hazardous environment and needs to travel to several places out there, a Wanderer. As the Wanderers meet in the Hub, their current starting location, they figure out it might be safer to travel together and accept some detours. The Wanderers and the local Map are created in chapter Preparation.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;During the main part of the game, the Wanderers sit together and plan their route, trying to find a compromise for everyone. If that is not possible, individual or multiple Wanderers may leave the group to form an alternative Traveling Party.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The game is finished by the Journey in which the actual trip of the one or several Traveling Parties is resolved and narrated. Each Wanderer will also receive a Score, how well they did.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;At the very end of this document you will find a short chapter named Settings, which contains ideas for a few scenarios in which you might want to play this game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Have fun!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="940" value="Action / Adventure" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25811" value="2014 RPG Geek 24 Hour RPGs" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2083" value="Core Rules (min needed to play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2114" value="Cards (cards drive the action)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2657" value="Competitive (players compete against each other to win)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2099" value="Description Based (Narrative more so than Dice)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2098" value="Trait / Aspect Based (personality affects gameplay)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1001" value="(Web published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="64781" value="Achim Zien" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="65144" value="Johnny Automatic" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="64781" value="Achim Zien" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>