<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="166880">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Cooking Mama 5: Bon Appetit!" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>The original kitchen diva that created the cooking genre is set to school you with brand new mouth-watering recipes and household mini-games. Cook your way through classic fare, exotic cultural dishes and sweet treats to delight the palate! Fun stylus-based activities will keep you busy around the house and prove to Mama that you&amp;rsquo;ve got the culinary chops to play in her kitchen!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The latest addition in the successful Mama franchise: 13 million+ games sold worldwide!&amp;#10;Unlock 60+ recipes as you progress. Test your skills with new appetizers, drinks, main dishes and desserts including: pork cutlet rice bowl, chicken nuggets, BBQ skewers, pumpkin gratin, raisin bread, Hawaiian pancakes, gingerbread cookies and much more!&amp;#10;Step out of the kitchen and help Mama with more than 30 new activities around the shop and house: feed the pets, deliver orders, make change, serve ice cream, wash dishes, pick apples, organize, draw and more.&amp;#10;Six gameplay modes feature intuitive stylus-based activities:&amp;#10;Let&amp;rsquo;s Cook: Create recipes step-by-step with Mama on hand to help you.&amp;#10;Cooking Dojo: Earn medals in timed challenges that reward you for quick and accurate preparation.&amp;#10;Help the Store: Work the register and play waitress at Mama&amp;rsquo;s Burger Shop.&amp;#10;Help Harvest: Gather your recipe fixins&amp;rsquo; before you cook.&amp;#10;Let&amp;rsquo;s Help Mama: Step outside the kitchen and assist Mama as CEO of the household with fresh activities that make &amp;ldquo;chores&amp;rdquo; fun and rewarding.&amp;#10;Let&amp;rsquo;s Study: Number and word games mix up the kitchen fun.&amp;#10;Earn furniture and decorations via SpotPass to customize your menus and game screens. Make your kitchen your own with stained glass, wallpaper, picture frames, plants, holiday items and more. You can even customize Mama&amp;rsquo;s outfit!&amp;#10;Single cart download play offers multiplayer cook offs for up to four players.&amp;#10;Gyroscope and accelerometer support for certain recipes.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Publisher Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Cooking Mama 5: Bon App&amp;eacute;tit! (&amp;#227;&amp;#130;&amp;#175;&amp;#227;&amp;#131;&amp;#131;&amp;#227;&amp;#130;&amp;#173;&amp;#227;&amp;#131;&amp;#179;&amp;#227;&amp;#130;&amp;#176;&amp;#227;&amp;#131;&amp;#158;&amp;#227;&amp;#131;&amp;#158;&amp;#239;&amp;#188;&amp;#149; Kukkingu Mama 5) is the sequel to the Nintendo 3DS video game Cooking Mama 4: Kitchen Magic and is the fifth installment to the Cooking Mama series on the Nintendo 3DS. It was released in Japan on November 21, 2013 and released on September 16, 2014 in North America. It contains over 60 recipes and new household activities/games.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: Wikipedia, &amp;quot;Cooking Mama 5: Bon App&amp;#195;&amp;#169;tit!&amp;quot;, available under the CC-BY-SA License.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="5857" value="Nintendo 3DS" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2156" value="Simulation" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2624" value="Food / Cooking" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameseries" id="5405" value="Cooking Mama" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2310" value="Network Multiplayer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="4" />
						               				<releasedate value="2013-11-21" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="12281" value="Cooking Mama Limited" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="12126" value="Majesco Entertainment" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="5857" name="nintendo3ds" friendlyname="Nintendo 3DS Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>