<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166846">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/c8IJCiN6niBElsvjVteSruG1LYc=/fit-in/200x150/pic2257584.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/MD6_NtwWFjd7IC_3AAqcAK_8G-8=/0x0/pic2257584.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Border Fort" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This Product is a full-color, 24 x 20 inch map of a Border Fort, and includes the VTT (Virtual Table top) files.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;ldquo;I knew it: As soon as the wooden gates fell off I realized we were dead men walking.&amp;rdquo;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Do you have what it takes to keep the border safe? DramaScape is looking for some mercenaries to keep it secure.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The product is a single external map of the surroundings, walls, and courtyard of a small border fortress with an internal map of the inner keep&amp;rsquo;s three rooms.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Border Fort is intended for use in fantasy games. One idea for a more modern game is to fill the border fort with a tank or tank destroyer group for the Germans that have run out of gasoline. The tanks are placed at the gate making them immobile forward facing artillery. With artillery and flak guns behind the tanks in the courtyard, the allies can&amp;rsquo;t leave this defensive strong point behind their lines. The Allies decide to flank the Germans on the eastern side of the fort by ramming a tank through the weak wooden wall to get the troops in&amp;hellip;if the convoy can make it past the artillery. If the player characters can take out the flak guns, they can call in an air strike on the fortress as well.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Adventure Hook for use with this map:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Invasion! The group has run afoul of a massive band of enemies along a supposedly peaceful border. A chase ensues with the band trying to hunt them down, mistaking them for border patrol scouts. The group spots the border fort in the distance during the chase and can decide to go towards the fortress or bravely try to divert them away from the fort.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;If they reach the fort, they find the gates open with no doors. The three or four guards at the fortress see the massive horde and realize their plight. The group needs to either help the guards fend off the horde or failing that cut a path through to escape and reach the capital to warn the king (Our Western Keep make can be used as the capital of the kingdom).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="184" value="History" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="23493" value="DramaScape Pay What You Want" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="DramaScape Free Volume 30" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="23830" value="DramaScape" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>