<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166834">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/TyalQzSI7Om-NP2N08woLcZrxjU=/fit-in/200x150/pic2257594.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/6_2g5VtaNRIZJBxAQm0nlWa8_Go=/0x0/pic2257594.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Zebbagrulom: King of the Eye F***ers" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="1652" value="Labyrinth Lord" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Deep within the bowels of the Earth there lives a strange race of magical creatures. They appear to be a giant, floating eyeball with thin, flexible arms flanking a wide and blubbering mouth, and both ragged-looking wings and a reptilian tail extending from its rear side. Some say they were born from the eye of Blorcas, god of wizards, when Gozmo Zalandros stole it and absorbed its power. But Blorcas has been blind and speechless, floating inert through the astral darkness, for near ten thousand years, if the sages are to be believed. So perhaps the bards have it right when they sing of Qianoa summoning them from beyond the scope of Saturn with her rituals.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Whatever their source, they have been a thorn in the side of human expansion for centuries, crawling out of their caves to wreak havoc and mayhem. But recently, the situation has taken a turn for the worse, for now they have a ruler to unite them in their malevolence. Zebbagrulom has crowned himself the king of the eye fuckers, and he has so far led them to victory against all the underground kingdoms they have met in battle. If his effusive braggadocio is indeed the truth, he has countless slaves and soldiers at his beck and call.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Zebbagrulom rules over his subterranean empire, and the other eye fuckers, with an iron fist and a honeyed tongue. He knows how to successfully organize all types of criminal enterprise, and he speaks all the tongues of the upper world. Completely lacking in remorse for the fates of other races, he trades in all manner of vices, inhumane diversions, and shady goods.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="25930" value="Monthly Monsters" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Monthly Monster 14-09LL-Bonus" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28236" value="Red Box Vancouver" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78226" value="Nathan Jones" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="19782" value="Johnstone Metzger" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>