<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="166904">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/vs3NWRaLUMJwSIVK6Ky3vSH3l9M=/fit-in/200x150/pic2257730.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/A9B79jsK7mZuML11oGGZ7V_Mtzw=/0x0/pic2257730.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Logging Camp" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This Product is a 48 x 30 inch, full color battlemap of a Logging Camp.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Product comes with the Square, Hex and No Overlay versions and the Virtual Tabletop Maps (VTT).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s get this section of the forest done. If we clear the whole area, one round of drinks on me at the Lumberjack Tavern tonight!&amp;rdquo;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Grab your axe and go. There is money to be made in the forest with DramaScape&amp;rsquo;s Logging Camp!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Logging Camp is a single exterior map of a lumberjack&amp;rsquo;s encampment in the center of a forest.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Logging Camp is intended for fantasy games. It could also be used as a modern map if you replaced the carts and ox with pickup trucks on the map and added some more modern construction equipment used for logging such as a crane and abulldozer.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Adventure Hook for use with this map:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Hatchets for Hire: The group is hired as mercenary guards to watch over the ox and cart bringing lumber to and from town and to guard the camps at night. The lumberjacks work all day and then drink all night at our Lumberjack&amp;rsquo;s Tavern. After stumbling out of the Lumberjack&amp;rsquo;s Tavern, they return to our Forest Camp to sleep the night. At night, they need guards to watch over the Logging Camp and Forest Camp to prevent people from stealing their stuff and ambushing them in the middle of the night. A druid is not happy with the lumberjacks&amp;rsquo; deforestation of his woods and sends a group of wolves to murder the lumberjacks in the middle of the night and animated trees to smash the logging camp. If the group manages to stop the animated trees and wolves, the spoor of the wolves and swath of destruction left by the moving trees leads them to the druid&amp;rsquo;s power source and base, our Grove of Hands map.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="184" value="History" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="23489" value="DramaScape Fantasy" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="DramaScape Fantasy Volume 044" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="23830" value="DramaScape" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>