<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167074">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/5TkcLCjxDATd_SikMHGxrYN38Rs=/fit-in/200x150/pic2259304.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/mjVm2Ved-8OFfKSQCvglyoPvzxg=/0x0/pic2259304.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Jedi Purge" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="4279" value="Fiasco" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Well, that happened. Palpatine killed the Republic, killed the Jedi too. Now it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;the New Order&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;the Empire&amp;rdquo;, take your pick. He has a personal enforcer now, Darth Vader, who seems intent on tracking down every last surviving Jedi and sending them to hell. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough just to break them, I guess.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Palpatine&amp;rsquo;s a hero. He ended the Clone Wars, brought the Separatists under control, and showed the people of the Known Galaxy that they don&amp;rsquo;t need the Jedi after all. That&amp;rsquo;s what the holos say, anyway. On the surface, it&amp;rsquo;s all flowers and candy for the average Imperial citizen. The average human Imperial citizen, that is.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It&amp;rsquo;s a different story, if you hang out where I hang out. I hear whispers of people gathering in secret to take on the new Emperor, to end his reign before things get really bad. It&amp;rsquo;ll be a hard sell - the man on the street is pretty much on the government&amp;rsquo;s side. The new Empire also has eyes and ears everywhere. Think wrong, breathe wrong, and they&amp;rsquo;ll find you, make you disappear before anyone notices.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The halls of power haven&amp;rsquo;t changed much either, still just people grabbing for more of what people in power want - that is, more power. They&amp;rsquo;ve just got more, better chances to do it now that everything&amp;rsquo;s been shaken up. The corruption people complained about in the Senate? It isn&amp;rsquo;t about to go away... in fact, it&amp;rsquo;s readying up to get a lot worse.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;And then you have the people on the Fringe. Scoundrels, criminals, whatever you want to call them. Every thief, grifter, and smuggler this side of Nal Hutta is out looking for some way to make a quick score off of the transition.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;New Order? Sounds more like New Chaos to me.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bad feeling about this.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="162" value="Science Fiction (Space Opera)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgsetting" id="1010" value="Star Wars" />
		
									
			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2099" value="Description Based (Narrative more so than Dice)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2089" value="GM-less (No gamemaster needed to play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1001" value="(Web published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="13432" value="Leonard Balsera" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="3" value="(Uncredited)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="13432" value="Leonard Balsera" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>