<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="167090">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="The Sun at Night" />
			
						                               				
				<name type="alternate" sortindex="1" value="The Sun at Night:  Part One" />
			
						               													<description>The tide of Soviet power washing across the face of the Earth could possibly have been turned back at various stages of history. But the new energy sources they discovered lit a fire under the Russian war machine. So when Stalin rolled into Paris, the resulting flare-up of global conflict left little more than smoking ash heaps where America and Great Britain had been.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Now, Stalin is dead. Though resistance movements have emerged, the Soviets still stand supreme as rulers of the globe. Only a force from beyond the earth could possibly tip the balance.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Abram Krupin, leader of a resistance cell, knows this. When he sees a dog fall from the stars, then, he takes it as an omen. This dog speaks, wears silver armor, and has an arsenal of mysterious weapons. Abram calls her Laika.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Laika believes that, despite all odds, she can protect the countless lives crushed by the Soviets.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Sun at Night is a 2D action platformer to be released in three parts. Part one is set for release Feb 4, 2014. All episodes will feature:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;     Massive, nonlinear levels that model the layouts of real locations in a way not yet seen in other platformers&amp;#10;     Large, choice-rich skill trees that let players approach the game the way they want to&amp;#10;     A novel defensive mechanic that lets players turn the firepower of Laika's enemies against them&amp;#10;     Smoothly flowing, fast-paced shooting action&amp;#10;     A story of struggle and hope, full of twists and revelations&amp;#10;     Rich, evocative art depicting a world dominated by a technologically ascendant Soviet empire&amp;#10;     Secrets and rewards hidden in every corner for the determined player&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Developer Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2147" value="Action" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2164" value="Platform" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2427" value="Alternate Historical" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="1" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-02-04" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="28275" value="Minicore Studios" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="28275" value="Minicore Studios" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="4" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>