<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167022">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/vrVeeDDjmY81_5cIQ6KW53ms88Q=/fit-in/200x150/pic2259012.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/OZjIlTva08W9p-eGli08afrYqE0=/0x0/pic2259012.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="East Sea Ire" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="4279" value="Fiasco" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Sindo is well off the east coast of South Korea, close to the international sea border of its sister country to the north. Almost 1 hour by a daily ferry is the only way to get to this small island. Village life in this sleepy fishing town has been quiet, but things are stirring.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A Seoul construction mogul has been kicking around the idea of building a huge resort. This planned project is garnering some wrath from a few locals which appreciate slow village life, especially a particular Buddhist monk and an old ajeossi.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Pickings for romantic partners are slim, and living in a small town means everyone knows your business, or at least wants to know, making discretion the key to any lover&amp;rsquo;s tryst. Dutiful husbands have been known to stray however, occasionally calling in a few mainland girls for a relatively harmless night of drinks and nori bang. But Kang&amp;rsquo;s love motel nearby never seems to hurt for business on Saturday nights.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The provincial fisheries official has been snooping around the docks, with rumors of looking into reports of illegal fishing. New businesses depend on old village money, with some saying kickbacks (along with proper forms in triplicate) being standard procedure for dealing with the village council office. Not to mention the few island farmers getting more irate at a local market owner for bringing in additional produce from the mainland.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;All the while some whisper about ships meeting out on the international sea border at night, with strange cargo being transferred between them. The sun may rise in the east, but things are shaping up for it to set in a sea of fire and blood.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2012" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="945" value="Crime" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="278" value="Culture (Asian / Far Eastern)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="550" value="Modern" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2099" value="Description Based (Narrative more so than Dice)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2089" value="GM-less (No gamemaster needed to play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1001" value="(Web published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78327" value="Geek Ken" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78327" value="Geek Ken" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="78327" value="Geek Ken" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>