<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167024">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/tRMKv8aRGJ6SfuPgpEG_FLZbS5I=/fit-in/200x150/pic2259022.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/NleknygEEoyCudUo7v71TBxfysM=/0x0/pic2259022.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Freeport 2717" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="4279" value="Fiasco" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It is the year 2717 and you are on the Space Station Freeport. An unaligned outpost, it&amp;rsquo;s the last space station before the intergalactic hyper-jump spot, leading to a nearly infinite number of worlds. You may wonder if the hyper-jump spot is so amazing why it&amp;rsquo;s on the farthest flung spot in the entire galaxy. That&amp;rsquo;s because not all the neighbors are friendly and not everyone who jumps gets to come home. Developed one hundred and fifty years ago, the hyper-jump spot creates a wormhole that can target other galaxies. With a second hyper-jump spot in place you can jump back and forth with relative safety. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t always a jump network though. It used to be the first jump spot could fling you across the universe and leave you there. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly how the network was built. Brave men and women on ships would make the jump to spots unknown. If they survived, they built new jump spots that let them come home. If a ship couldn&amp;rsquo;t return, most assumed the destination was too dangerous and didn&amp;rsquo;t jump there again.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;We get all types here: Local business folks who make the station their home. Alliance officers on shore leave before making the jump, Smugglers, Thieves, and Pirates mingling with Con Men and Mercenaries in the stations Shops, Clubs, Bars and Casino. All under the ever watchful eye of the Ministry of Light, and station security of course.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;There is always something new and exciting to see, but unfortunately, it might just be the last thing you see.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="945" value="Crime" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="162" value="Science Fiction (Space Opera)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2099" value="Description Based (Narrative more so than Dice)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2089" value="GM-less (No gamemaster needed to play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1001" value="(Web published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78328" value="Ken Schaefer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78329" value="Matt Schaefer" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78328" value="Ken Schaefer" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="78328" value="Ken Schaefer" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="78329" value="Matt Schaefer" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>