<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167018">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/9mjBNpQfo_X5dvOTAgX9zt68dY0=/fit-in/200x150/pic2273443.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/_MyHMHBVUyXSLQqa75vXYpuLD0g=/0x0/pic2273443.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Guardians of Good" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="2791" value="Pathfinder System Compatible Product" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;From Good to GREAT!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Good-aligned creatures are vastly outnumbered in roleplaying games, for the obvious reason that most of the time the characters are the heroes of the stories and they are unlikely to fight the powers of good. However, in a mythic world of mythic threats from the forces of darkness, there is a need for a mythic response, and here you will find it: the Guardians of Good! These mighty monsters stand just a little lower than the angels in purity of heart, but are second to none in strength of spirit as unconquerable bastions against evil. Here you will find the mighty metallic dragons, from the young brass to adult copper,  giant adult bronze and ancient silver, all the way up to the great wyrm gold dragon. Beyond such winged wonders are the feathered serpents of the jungle, the couatl, along side the shedu, tauric guardians of the deep desert and the lammasu, the winged lions of heaven. Friendly but fierce blink dogs and luck-bearing ceru are also found within, alongside seagoing tritons and the secretive yet stalwart swan maiden. As if a dozen and one goodly guardians from CR 3 to 28 were not enough, we bring you the wise and noble chiron, immortal centaur mentor to aspiring heroes and trainer in the arts of the mind and heart as well as with bow and blade. Beyond these beatific beasts, we also bring you eight brand-new feats, including both non-mythic and mythic versions, to represent the mysteries of devotion to the cause of weal and righteousness that will help your heroes carry the day against any enemy.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="23661" value="Mythic Monsters" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="27419" value="Mythic Plug-Ins" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="Mythic Monsters 20" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="24908" value="Legendary Games" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="16891" value="Jason Nelson" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36352" value="Mike Welham" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="67630" value="Mike Lowe" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="14055" value="Rick Hershey" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="70434" value="Alistair Rigg" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>