<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167182">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/5PxegXTPYV6Uxu8eGquqj_MxkTY=/fit-in/200x150/pic2261093.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/dAb4BP9pYtLhuawosOuLA3HQmRI=/0x0/pic2261093.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Ghosts of Opal Ditch" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="9854" value="Cthulhu Dark (Original Version)" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;For the last couple of years, the SkyFy Channel had fallen behind in the rating wars. Their programs suffered from uninspired writing and terrible acting, they cranked out underfunded and unoriginal monster-of-the-week movies, and an unwise investment in obtaining the television rights to amateur boxing nearly forced them into bankruptcy.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Two seasons ago, a new show debuted on SkyFy that changed everything: Spirit Seekers. Part myth investigation, part ghost hunting, and all sensationalized reality show, the hosts and crew of Spirit Seekers explored abandoned buildings and gutted houses, recorded highly unlikely evidence of supernatural encounters, and featured B-list guest celebrities who were more embarrassing than entertaining.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;And the audience loved it. The ratings for the fist season went through the roof, beating out many popular prime-time shows on better cable channels. With advertisers signing on in droves, the second season was moved to compete directly with heavyweights like Myth Hunters and American Idol. Again, their ratings skyrocketed, with specials filmed in an old insane asylum, a neglected naval base, and even a former WWII internment camp.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Now, as they plan their third season, the writers have proposed a special two-hour episode. Fans had been writing in on the Spirit Seekers blog and FaceSpace page about rumors from New South Wales, Australia. Apparently four or fie years ago a&amp;#10;Japanese television crew for a similar, occult-themed program &amp;ndash; Naruhodo Noroi &amp;ndash; went missing while filming in a derelict mining camp called Opal Ditch. The locals reported that they had vanished into the Dreamlands.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Of course, to the SkyFy program executives, this sounded like a bunch of nonsense. However, fact-checkers soon uncovered that a Japanese TV crew did in fact go missing there, and only one of the crew had been found with amnesia nine months later in a rain-gorged creek nearly six kilometers south of the camp. This caught the attention of Spirit Seekers'' producer, and, after securing a financial partnership with the CEO of Saxxon Petroleum, got the green light for the Season Three Premiere.&amp;#10;With contracts signed and immunizations updated, the cast and crew get ready to board their flight to a small town called Lightning Ridge.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2013" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="988" value="Horror (Cthulhu Mythos)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="946" value="Modern (Pop Culture)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2099" value="Description Based (Narrative more so than Dice)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2112" value="Dice (Primarily d6)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2117" value="Roll and keep (4k2 means roll 4 and keep 2)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28271" value="Gremlin Legions" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="62949" value="Mike Wight" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="62949" value="Mike Wight" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="62949" value="Mike Wight" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="1" />
			<average value="5" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="2" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="1" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>