<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167353">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/Yv_aobgoICQUXgHUiaM9yQ6x81Y=/fit-in/200x150/pic2264205.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/TwTta7GiBPFrKiNQhojO_gFOoXs=/0x0/pic2264205.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Launch Bay" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This product is a full-color, 48 inch by 20 inch, floor plan of a Launch Bay, with Hex, Square and No overlay.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The PDF includes includes the VTT (Virtual Table Top Images for online play).&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;ldquo;Emergency! Explosion on the flight deck! Enemy boarding party! Space marines to the flight deck!&amp;rdquo;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;DramaScape launches into space again with our latest map!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Launch Bay is an interior map of a futuristic hangar with a control room for coordination of take-off and landing of fighters. This is suitable for use as the landing bay of a space carrier, air carrier (can&amp;rsquo;t operate in space, only in a planetary atmosphere), or a terrestrial airbase on a planet.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Launch Bay is intended for use in near or far-future science fiction games.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Adventure hook for use with this map:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Space Carrier War: Two space carriers face off, launching small fighters from their launch bays to destroy the enemy space carrier&amp;rsquo;s fleet with a second wave of small bombers with fighter escorts to finish off the enemy carrier. An enemy landing party crashes into the landing bay and then slides on top of the lift to prevent more fighters and bombers from being deployed. From the wreckage, robots use welding lasers to get out of the wrecked ship, wielding them to kill anyone in the way of their target, the command and control of the landing bay. Once they get to the doors of command and control, they use the welding lasers to breach the doors and get inside, attempting to kill the officers inside.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Player Characters are space marines that rush to the landing bay to defeat the robots and defend the officers and the engineers who need to clear the deck of the wreck with construction mech suits to get to the lift and repair it. The space battle raging outside the ship becomes desperate for the player&amp;rsquo;s side as the expected reinforcements are not forthcoming while the lift is down.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Once the space marines restore the lift, they take the next bomber (and possibly fighters) in a mission of vengeance against the enemy space carrier. Perhaps even using a boarding ship to transport themselves into the enemy landing bay and return the favor by fragging the enemy&amp;rsquo;s commanders.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="183" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="23497" value="DramaScape SciFi" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="DramaScape SciFi Volume 31" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="23830" value="DramaScape" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>