<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167480">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/iL7pM1S6VQ0vKoboeSOFiy1qbCQ=/fit-in/200x150/pic2267575.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/K8G-Me-D9x9TeZ0vRVkX0MHCvwM=/0x0/pic2267575.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Fey Heritage" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="2791" value="Pathfinder System Compatible Product" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Unlock a New Kind of Mythic Power!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Sure, your character&amp;rsquo;s mythic path tells you about the kinds of abilities in which he specializes, and perhaps even gives some clue as to his ultimate mythic destiny, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t say anything about where he came from, and what made him mythic in the first place. For that, you can turn to a mythic heritage. This new aspect of mythic characters allows for further customization of your mythic character. A mythic character can choose a mythic heritage in addition to his or her mythic path, and doing so grants him access to a number of unique abilities that are designed to reflect the flavor of his heritage, while also being of value to characters of every mythic path.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This installment introduces the fey heritage, for characters who are in some way touched by or related to the mysterious and wild powers of the fey. They might be related through blood, either distantly or directly, to one or more creatures of the fey kingdom, or they may have simply earned the favor of a powerful faerie who chose to grant them a touch of her gifts. The character may have been a changeling, stolen from his nurse to be raised among the fair folk, or he may be ignorant of the origins of his power, discovering the fey&amp;rsquo;s touch only as circumstances reveal where his abilities come from.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Whatever its cause, this mythic heritage allows you to harness the great cosmic powers of the heavens. This book includes 22 new mythic abilities, which together make up the fey mythic heritage. From magical sleep and memory loss arrows to smiles that are literally enchanting and a variety of powerful glamers, this book grants you access to all the iconic powers of the fey.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="24357" value="Mythic Mastery" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="11870" value="Necromancers of the Northwest" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="9731" value="Josh Cappel" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36373" value="Alex Riggs" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="3" value="(Uncredited)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="36376" value="Rosa Riggs" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>