<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="167491">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Stardust Colonies" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>Stardust Colonies is a unique sci-fi RTS where you colonize and defeat alien planets. Gather resources, build up your base and complete mission objectives. Micro-manage actions and emotions of your minions so that your race can survive and succeed. Customise your mothership and choose between abilities that will challenge your morality.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;- Complete mission objectives like building monuments, securing an area or defeating enemy bases &amp;#10;- Micro-manage your minions by assigning them to jobs they like and are good at &amp;#10;- Let your minions take a break to make them more effective at work &amp;#10;- Build light beacons to repel alien creatures that want to steal your resources &amp;#10;- Train soldiers to eliminate hostile aliens &amp;#10;- Take care of the basic needs of the colony: provide food, water, light, power &amp;#10;- Make your minions happy by creating beautifications and entertainment for them &amp;#10;- Customise your capabilities by buying and researching upgrades for your mothership using resources and intelligence gathered during missions &amp;#10;- Colonize procedurally generated side-quest planets to secure a stable resource income&amp;#10;&amp;#10;SPECIAL GAME FEATURES&amp;#10;- Procedural maps. Missions feel and look a bit different every time you play them &amp;#10;- Realistic fog of war, using only line of sight of units and buildings &amp;#10;- Good, evil or pragmatic? Become the kind of colonizator you want to be &amp;#10;- Show off your skills and achievements on an on-line profile &amp;#10;- Original 3D graphics &amp;#10;- Survival-style minimalistic user interface&amp;#10;&amp;#10;BACKGROUND STORY&amp;#10;It is year 4860 and gorgans have become a successful species of scientists and explorers. They use the lower lorkans for all physical work and manage to control them almost perfectly using long-range telepathy. Gorgans live off the Universe itself - they colonize untouched planets and use acquired resources to progress even further. As a Colonizator, you will be given a chance to create your own intergalactic empire by generating an income, researching technology and upgrading your mothership. You can become a generous and caring explorer of the vast space or a powerful and merciless ruler. Or something in between.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Game Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2166" value="Real Time Strategy" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2264" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="1" />
						               				<releasedate value="2013-11-01" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="4" value="(Self-Published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="4" value="(Self-Published)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>