<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167659">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/W5dCIINRw1UjnBJ_eIYRbzW7L-U=/fit-in/200x150/pic2271662.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/Qt-4u4rqWmgxv771cpjmWbOeFJ0=/0x0/pic2271662.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Firefly Vornhack Complete Space and Sci-fi Kit" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From the Introduction:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Simply put Vornheim the Complete City Kit is one of the most useful and enjoyable role-playing books I've ever used. I feel there are quite a few novel ideas in Vornheim that make a Game Master's job easier, and keep the action and focus on happenings at the table and not flipping through pages of a book.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;[...]&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Zak's whole &amp;quot;hack Vornheim and create something so I don't have to write it myself&amp;quot; attitude is awesome and something that made me really want to use Vornheim as inspiration and a guide for this project.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;As a Game Master I run fantasy (usually weird and dark and gritty), horror, and science fiction. Vornheim needs little alteration as a city kit for use in a fantasy setting, but science fiction is a whole different ball game. My sci-fi games frequently are set in the Firefly Universe created by Joss Whedon (I won't gush on why I love the setting so much) and I knew I wanted to hack Vornheim to be an aid for me while running the game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Truth be told, I created this hack for myself, as an aid for quick and easy game running, but put so much damned work into it that I wanted to share it with others. There are ideas, suggestions, etc in these charts and tables that are very specific to the Firefly universe, but file the numbers off and they will easily fit a different sci-fi setting, others are not so specific.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Feel free to use these tables as you see fit! Keep with the philosophy outlined in the Vornheim book and have a great time enjoying this awesome hobby!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;So grab some friends, grab some dice, and keep rolling!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2012" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="183" value="Science Fiction" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgsetting" id="287" value="The 'Verse" />
		
									
			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2107" value="Campaign Setting (game world)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1001" value="(Web published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="41390" value="Mike Evans" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="3" value="(Uncredited)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="41390" value="Mike Evans" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>