<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167605">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/UaKZkqKaGD71ge6z26B7n33DS3I=/fit-in/200x150/pic2271239.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/P8dbKzjyJAJm4AaELsHuTJwe_64=/0x0/pic2271239.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Kugelberg Flood" />
			
						                               				
				<name type="alternate" sortindex="1" value="Kugelburg Flood" />
			
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>designer's blurb&amp;#10; A vanilla fantasy world one shot location/event focused on plundering the cursed pleasure dome of an ancient tyrant, now sunken beneath the sea.  The party will have twelve hours to explore the place and grab what they can while the sea is at a once every ten year magical ebb.  The dangers include a spectral odalisque, mad automatons, poison coral and a lot of zombie sea life. I suspect the dome could be run as a 1st level adventure, but the enemies are a bit tough for that.  Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s more appropriate for a 2nd level party. The greatest danger though is of course the return of the ocean so I think this thing would only work if one&amp;rsquo;s GM enjoyed timekeeping.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;from the introduction&amp;#10;The florid Kugelburgers slap their fleshy chests between bites of buttery pastry and black beer. They encourage vagabonds to move on in the morning, after a good meal. They have no need of bravos - the area is safe, devoid of ruins, brigandage and unnatural beasts, without jobs for rough men and women of war. Yet the sages and astrologers know that in three days the murky waters of Kugelburg&amp;rsquo;s wide bay will sink, retreating to the deep sea and unveiling the sunken dome of the palace of the last Voivode.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;user summary:&amp;#10;This adventure contains no creature statistics, but instead refers to them only by giving names and number appearing.  This scenario could be used with any type of old-school class-and-level fantasy game with very little preparation.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1001" value="(Web published)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="67804" value="Gus L" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="67804" value="Gus L" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="67804" value="Gus L" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>