<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="167732">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/bRPw9Tw6fSpHXuwNZ3Vr5gEx4y4=/fit-in/200x150/pic2640588.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/DiO9I_p7rEomNh57cQMxfxbAvi0=/0x0/pic2640588.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Hounds of Halthrag Keep" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="10737" value="Dungeon Crawl Classics Role Playing Game" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Long ago, as children, we flipped furiously through curious little tomes in which fate was delineated for us, Choosing Our Own Adventures, Fighting Furiously, little Wolf Pups All Alone under the covers, scribbling and erasing and picking entries&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Die, start over, repeat.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Now that we are Men and Women, and Whatevers, we have shiny new things and do them the way we like.  Dungeon Crawl Classics is a new thing, and this thing you see here is a way to blend that Old Peanut Butter with your Spiffy New Chocolate.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Hounds of Halthrag Keep is a story - the second oldest story - in which an innocent schmuck is plunged feet-first into the Flames of Truth and Adversity, to Die Badly or Win Big.  That's all it is.  It's hard.  It's unforgiving. It's relentless.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;It's a complicated funnel character generator, for you DCC folks in the know.  If you're not in the know, but you're interested in DCC, then what you get inside is a 80's-era throwback in PDF form, with digital hyperlinks so you can flip furiously back and forth and get the end that you want.  Shoehorned inside it is a subset of the Dungeon Crawl Classics rules, so that once you've mastered the contents, you'll know the Basic Ways of DCC and also have a hankering for the flavour.  Yes, the flavour.  I spell it that way for a reason.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;89 pages of random encounters, extradimensional evil, Appendix N-flavoured solo 0-level madness, sure to make you grit your teeth in aggravation and generate (should you escape it!) a pretty spiffy character ripe for tromping all over the multiverse in any DCC game with a little gonzo in it.  Explosive laser pistols, 0-level cantrips (gasp!), a bunch of pseudo-random tables, and a bunch of slimy bad guys that prey upon the innocent and that just beg for you to power up and open a can of whoop-ass on them!  It can be done, I assure you!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2136" value="Solitaire Adventure" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2121" value="Action Table (table determines action outcomes)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2132" value="Dice (Specialized)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2134" value="Random Attribute Generation (during Character Creation)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28406" value="The Hapless Henchman Press" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="74734" value="Noah Stevens" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="63733" value="Paul Wolfe" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="13893" value="Russ Nicholson" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78641" value="Sam Schultz" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="74734" value="Noah Stevens" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="74734" value="Noah Stevens" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="11" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>