<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="168045">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/4Ei6jPH6bNqvBNRbXd-hrEzKMUI=/fit-in/200x150/pic2281266.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/PSW7yXjSYEpPvu5hvZ5QXNjf9UU=/0x0/pic2281266.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Gothnog&#039;s Remarkable Spells: Uncanny Expansion" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="2791" value="Pathfinder System Compatible Product" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Gothong&amp;rsquo;s Remarkable Spells takes spell casting to a whole new level. These spells have been created by some of the most brilliant wizards of all time, places and dimensions, and have been collected &amp;mdash; often at great personal risk &amp;mdash; by Gothnog himself. Each installment contains only one spell, but each promises to be so beneficial to any arcane caster who decides to study them, there will be little doubt that it was worth the additional time and expense.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;One of the most remarkable aspects of these spells is that they evolve with the caster, becoming more and more useful as time goes on. For that reason, some have started calling them &amp;ldquo;legacy spells.&amp;rdquo; The cost for their exceptional usefulness is that the casting of these spells becomes correspondingly more complex, time&amp;#10;consuming and expensive as their power increases.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Another thing that sets these spells apart is that they do not operate within any traditional school of magic. The reason for this is not known, though some speculate that it is because they tend to access multiple&amp;#10;schools simultaneously, while others believe that they tap into a different kind of magic entirely.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Unlike Gothnog&amp;rsquo;s Magnificent Cantrips, these spells are not for the casual caster or arcane dabbler. Only serious arcane practitioners should attempt to learn and employ these formidable incantations.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This first spell is called Uncanny Expansion, and it allows the caster to increase the amount of useable space in almost any given vessel. This spell may one day make the Bag of Holding obsolete.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Please note that neither Gothnog, nor anyone involved with the publication of these spells, is responsible for any harm resulting from their use... or misuse. Good luck.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2012" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="26085" value="Gothnog's" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2133" value="Race Based (Player Race/Species affects gameplay)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2094" value="Skill Based (buy or gain skills)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="26843" value="Critical Hit Publishing" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="73900" value="Alex Guillotte" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="73900" value="Alex Guillotte" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="50279" value="Wikimedia Commons" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="73900" value="Alex Guillotte" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>