<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="168243">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/tR41h7ln5HszTP_3udB9bBXmKH8=/fit-in/200x150/pic2498456.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/IAs4KSoWZFJcfzfSqWIDzJS6BqU=/0x0/pic2498456.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Chaos 6010 A.D." />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="24178" value="Chaos 6010 A.D." />
		
									
			

			               													<description>Publisher's Description from their website:&amp;#10;This gritty, street punk style RPG was intended for mature readers. Then people whined that it was too dark so I censored this version for the kids. If it's too dark, then get a flash light you p!@#$.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;After the time of the Apocalypse and the Age of Darkness, a new empire has risen from the decadence of Earth. An alliance of humans and an ancient alien race known as the eldrynn have formed the Armethian Empire. Magic, technology, and the theocratic government known as &amp;quot;The Order&amp;quot; have strengthened the structure of the known galaxy. The might of the military have assimilated many races under its own rule through diplomacy and endless war. Yet now, in the Age of Adventure, demons from the sixth dimension have once again found their way to the primordial realm. Heroes and villains alike must choose their path to immortality, struggle to survive, and stop the hordes of darkness from consuming their own dimension.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;You must choose your own destiny. Crush your enemies with fist, blade, gun, and spell. Complete quests and missions for adventure, reputation, glory, wealth, and power. Stand alone, or as a part of a crew of powerful allies that struggle within a dark and distant future. Become mighty warriors or spell casters. Become heroes or villains that can reign powerful enough to create their own empires, and command their own armies. Select from over 20 different alien races and over 20 different character classes. Build your character to become as powerful as the immortals with over 100 levels of advancement. Choose from hundreds of different level advancement abilities and talents within a system that is designed for endless gameplay. You may even continue playing powerful characters after their death with rules for an afterlife campaign that moves into the sixth dimension. Thus the spirit world, where you may one day reach the status of angel or demon. You will discover how eternal the universe is with rules that let you travel across the multiverse while adventuring to new worlds, star systems, and galaxies.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Chaos 6010 A.D. allows for a completely upgradeable game system, encouraging you to create your own worlds, alien races, weapons, spells, monsters, or anything else that you might wish to design. There are plenty of random tables to help you construct these ideas, and adapt them to the system. Endless adventures await game masters and players of fantasy / sci-fi role-playing.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Be sure to check out Pray for Dawn, the very first module for Chaos 6010 A.D. This post apocalyptic, survival, horror throws the crew into 130 full color pages of twisted nightmares. Every street has a different tale and every house holds a wicked story. This module is intended for mature players and can be used for other games. It may also be played several times with many different outcomes and enemies. Pray for Dawn comes complete with a narrative if the game master is new or wishes to describe every detail of the massive Necropolis. This module will scare the !@#$ out of your players! Hope you enjoy!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2011" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="940" value="Action / Adventure" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="168" value="Fantasy (Science Fantasy)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="158" value="Horror" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="165" value="Science Fiction (Post Apocalypse)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2083" value="Core Rules (min needed to play)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="28471" value="Arcanum Syndicate" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="78808" value="Brandon Williams" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="78808" value="Brandon Williams" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="78809" value="Todd Bauman" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="78811" value="David Whiting" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="78810" value="Mandi Williams" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="1" />
			<average value="3" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="4" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="1" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>