<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="168259">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/ZwVMQeHpjffG4f1mkDdsrBoFNd4=/fit-in/200x150/pic2287593.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/rDaoFl5EC2hXwXR_x-X9D-aCEL4=/0x0/pic2287593.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Night of the Spirits" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="509" value="Castles &amp; Crusades" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>Publisher Blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;At the end of each year comes the month and holiday of Samonios, Samhain or Nos Galan Gaeaf, or Halloween. This is the time when the worlds are drawn together and monsters, gods and the spirits of ancestors wander between them. It is a dangerous and dark time in which the most holy and sacred of ideas mean more than they ever have before in the previous year. It is a time for the Dead and to honor them.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Events in the last year were steeped in bloody battles, the death of kings and encroaching evil from the Otherworld. The seers and madmen foretell that the omens are in place to bring a wrathful invasion from the Land of Magic. Most nobles and lords scoff at these superstitious words and ridicule them, but the common-folk know that there is truth in those portents and omens.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Families stay close, hold their festivities in honor of their ancestors and the gods, but stay wary of the dangers that might find their way into their darkened homes and lives. But for the young or unwary . . . .&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Little Addolgar ap Maelon Gof has wandered into the thick foliage of the Coed Celyddon, lured by the many colored playful lights that he saw dancing and laughing. Now the young dark haired child of ten winters is deep in the mist-shrouded forest soaked in Otherworld energies. A storm is brewing in the dark woods, stirring the trees and causing the limbs and boughs to crack and knock against each other. Owls hoot in their haunting voice and somewhere distant, wolves howl. Addolgar climbs over fallen trees and makes his way in bramble patches trying to get closer to the mysterious lights in the boughs of the trees.&amp;#10;Night of Spirits plunges you into the heart of Nos Galan Gaeaf, bringing your characters face to face with the Otherworld and the true horrors of the holiday!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Night of Spirits is an adventure for 3-5 characters of around 4th-6th level.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="155" value="Fantasy (High Fantasy)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="161" value="Mythology / Folklore" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgsetting" id="887" value="Aihrde" />
		
									
			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2084" value="Scenario / Adventure / Module" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2101" value="Attribute/Stat Based (STR, CON, PER, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2095" value="Class Based (Pilot, Wizard, Scientist, etc)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2088" value="Dice (Primarily d20)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2122" value="Dice (Various)" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgmechanic" id="2096" value="Level Based (Earn XP and level up)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="1477" value="Troll Lord Games" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="52299" value="Brian Young" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="15812" value="Peter Bradley" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="15812" value="Peter Bradley" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="5" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>