<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="168387">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/sOx-fv-zbFMd4qdSem1K9hIUSD4=/fit-in/200x150/pic2289268.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/xTI2NvFLF8Q0bSd_IubUKY2hpx4=/0x0/pic2289268.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Autumn Cemetery" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This is a 32 x 30 inch Battlemap of an Autumn Cemetery, it has Hex, Square and No Overlays, it also includes the VTT files for online play.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;ldquo;What do you mean I am dead?&amp;rdquo;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;DramaScape dares you to enter our Autumn Cemetery for your Halloween-themed games this year! A combination of fallen foliage from trees and creepy mausoleums and coffins make this map perfect for Horror games set in autumn.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Autumn Cemetery is a single exterior map of a well-maintained cemetery in the midst of fall season. The wind continues to howl and blow leaves all over the cemetery from the trees, much to the chagrin of the caretakers.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Autumn Cemetery is intended for use in horror and modern settings. It could also be easily used in fantasy settings as a cemetery with a high degree of reverence for those interred there explaining its well-maintained state.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Adventure Hook for use with this map:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Dead Man Talking: A local man was recently found dead under mysterious circumstances and then buried in the local cemetery. The locals say that they have seen this dead man lurking about town at night time. The player characters are playing detectives trying to figure out who murdered the man. With little evidence of foul play from the autopsy, they might decide to investigate the rumors.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;While in town at night, they see a man matching the dead man&amp;rsquo;s physical appearance wandering around town. He stops around his former house and gropes at the door handle of his own home, moaning in frustration that he is barred entry from his home. He then walks back to the cemetery glumly.&amp;#10;If the group follows him, they find that he is not alone. Many men and women are wandering around the old cemetery in various states of decay. If they see the detectives they wander up to them and moan in frustration as if trying to communicate but don&amp;rsquo;t attack them unless provoked. The detectives might recognize them as other people who were found dead of mysterious circumstances in the last year.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;When the recently dead man sees them he walks up to them and starts talking! He wants to know what happened to his possessions like his keys and wallet. He needs his keys to get back into his house and stop squatting in this cemetery.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The player characters can explain that he is dead, which makes the dead man confused and possibly angry, since he doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to realize he is dead. Or they can bluff him, pretending they have his keys and wallet and they&amp;rsquo;ll give them back after a few questions, maybe even promising to take him to the police station to give them back to him. The dead man doesn&amp;rsquo;t remember too much as if he has amnesia, but he might be able to reveal some clues about his killer, a witch doctor using drugs or herbs to kill people that then cause them to be brought back as zombies with the proper ritual. Those resurrected this way have some consciousness left, but it quickly fades away over time.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Another murder occurs in the next week unless the group confronts the witch doctor before then. The witch doctor is seen there at the funeral. If the group goes to the cemetery that very night, they can see the witch doctor performing a ritual surrounded by his human cronies and zombie thralls. It is time to stop the witch doctor lest he raise another zombie. His talking zombies apologize or look sad as they try to fight the group. When the witch doctor is defeated, the talking zombie thanks the group and other zombies seem to smile before walking to their coffins to finally rest in peace.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="158" value="Horror" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="550" value="Modern" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="23494" value="DramaScape Modern" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="DramaScape Modern Volume 35" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="23830" value="DramaScape" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="0" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>