<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="boardgame" id="168406">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="What da Blank" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>Overview&amp;#10;What Da Blank is a question-based card game where you and your friends are put in messed up situations and you get to come up with the best or worst answers or stories to make your friends laugh their butts off! It's really a game for friends to have laughter-filled, honest, friendship-insulting fun!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Rules&amp;#10;1. The player with the least hair will start the game by taking a card form the top of the deck.&amp;#10;2. The player will then read the question to the group,  replacing the blank with his/her name.&amp;#10;3. The other players will then take turns to give their best/most messed up answers they can think of.&amp;#10;4. The player will then pick the answer that he/she feels is the best answer and awards that person the card.&amp;#10;5. The next player will then take another card from the deck and the game continues.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Win Condition&amp;#10;The first player to get 3 cards wins the game! When a player has won, all cards will return to the deck and the deck will be reshuffled to &amp;quot;reset&amp;quot; the game.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Minus Cards&amp;#10;If any player draws a minus card, they must return the minus card and any two cards on their hand to the bottom of the deck. That player's turn is now over and the next player continues the game by taking a card from the deck.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Community Aspect&amp;#10;What makes What da Blank special is that most (if not all) the questions in the game were conceived from the creators' friends! Seeing this, the creators want to incorporate more questions into future expansions by getting crazy questions from the community to make a game that is truly community-inspired!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      	               				<yearpublished value="2015" />
						               				<minplayers value="3" />
						               				<maxplayers value="0" />
						      			<poll name="suggested_numplayers" title="User Suggested Number of Players" totalvotes="0">
			
		<results numplayers="0+">		
				</results>					
	</poll> 			               				<playingtime value="15" />
						               				<minplaytime value="15" />
						               				<maxplaytime value="15" />
						               				<minage value="0" />
						      			<poll name="suggested_playerage" title="User Suggested Player Age" totalvotes="0">
	</poll> 			      			<poll name="language_dependence" title="Language Dependence" totalvotes="0">
	</poll> 			      			 			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamecategory" id="1002" value="Card Game" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamecategory" id="1030" value="Party Game" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamemechanic" id="2047" value="Memory" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamemechanic" id="2027" value="Storytelling" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamefamily" id="22184" value="Admin: Unreleased Games" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamefamily" id="8374" value="Crowdfunding: Kickstarter" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      	      	      			

			      			

			      	      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="boardgamepublisher" id="4" value="(Self-Published)" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="1" name="boardgame" friendlyname="Board Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>