<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="168498">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/uWDC7t7BUv4N5Nb0eN6CpD567uo=/fit-in/200x150/pic2290970.png</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/bZAYU7UesHRhKmKkhx2lVcwCUVU=/0x0/pic2290970.png</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="5" value="The Mythos Society Guide to New England" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>from publisher's announcement:&amp;#10;This expansive universal sourcebook by veteran game designer Clint Staples can be used to enhance any horror, mystery or adventure roleplaying scenarios set in New England. It is particularly suited for Mythos-oriented games like Call of Cthulhu and Cthulhu Live. It is also a fun and provocative read for anyone interested in the esoteric history of New England, and a resource for stories or other projects that have horror or the weird as themes; are based on/or inspired by the works of H. P. Lovecraft or other Cthulhu Mythos authors; or are set during the period between the two World Wars.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Mythos Guide to New England provides a record of the land and its inhabitants, its prehistory and history, and its natural and unnatural characteristics. In these pages you will find tales of the witchcraft, hauntings, monsters and malevolence that have plagued the people of the region, from pre-Colonial days into the 20th Century.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;New England is a diverse territory. Some of the earliest settlements in the New World lie check by jowl with rugged country that, to this day, is all but untraveled by humanity. The sea, with its rocky shoals, rugged coves, unknown depths, and centuries of legend and lore holds sway over the minds of the region's inhabitants. The mountains and forests are just as mysterious and deadly, keeping secrets centuries and even millennia old, some of which mankind would be better off not knowing. Between these wild areas are the settled portions, farms and orchards inland and harbors filled with ships, and the folk that sail them on the coast. Man prevails in such places, but in the shadowed lanes, forgotten cellars, and flightless passages beneath his world, there is still much that is unknown and unsettling.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="988" value="Horror (Cthulhu Mythos)" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgsetting" id="2572" value="Cthulhu Classic (1920s &amp; 1930s)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			               				<seriescode value="" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2108" value="Sourcebook (rules/options to enhance play)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="8013" value="Skirmisher Publishing" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="28833" value="Clint Staples" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="14560" value="Bradley McDevitt" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="34801" value="William T. Thrasher" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="12150" value="Michael O. Varhola" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="13" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="1" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>