<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="rpgitem" id="168542">
         <thumbnail>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/thumb/img/P0t9aGUr9YS16AIWytuz_HRREKI=/fit-in/200x150/pic2292934.jpg</thumbnail>
      <image>https://cf.geekdo-images.com/original/img/0f8p-egS2HRA-J8EBQLH0a2beaA=/0x0/pic2292934.jpg</image>
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Vine Maze" />
			
						                           
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpg" id="356" value="Generic / Universal" />
		
									
			

			               													<description>From publisher blurb:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;This Product is a full-color, 16 x 20 inch map of a Vine Maze, and includes the VTT (Virtual Table top) files.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;ldquo;This guy is so rich we will be set for life. All we need to do is get through his maze to get to his mansion.&amp;rdquo;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Vine Maze is a single external map of a simple maze with patches of spreading vines.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Vine Maze is intended for use in fantasy or horror games. It could also be used in a modern game as a courtyard of a rich man who doesn&amp;rsquo;t like visitors to his house.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Adventure hook for use with this map:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;A Maze to Money: A thief asks the group to help him get through a maze to get to a rich merchant&amp;rsquo;s mansion. He has all the skills needed to get rife through the mansion, but he is worried about the merchant&amp;rsquo;s soldier guards and needs the group as muscle and backup.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;The Maze entrance is left unguarded, an inauspicious sign, as if the merchant is daring you to enter. The vines near the entrance undulate in the wind, but are just normal vines.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Patrols can be found within the maze made up of human soldiers. But the greatest threat in the maze is the vines that attack anyone that does not bare a talisman with the merchant&amp;rsquo;s head as a symbol. The patrols all have these talismans. The bloodthirsty vines use their thorns to pierce flesh and then suck blood out the same way most plants suck water out of the earth from those not wearing the enchanted talisman. The thief is the first one to be attacked and likely dies from the assault. Now it&amp;rsquo;s up to the player characters to decide to continue onwards to the merchant&amp;rsquo;s mansion or retreat from the deadly plants.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										               				<yearpublished value="2014" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="961" value="Fantasy" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpggenre" id="158" value="Horror" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgseries" id="23493" value="DramaScape Pay What You Want" />
		
									
			

			               				<seriescode value="DramaScape Free Volume 31" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgcategory" id="2086" value="Accessory (dice, maps, screens, cards)" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgpublisher" id="23830" value="DramaScape" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgdesigner" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgartist" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="36704" value="Steven J. Black" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="rpgproducer" id="26563" value="Simon Powell" />
		
									
			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="0" />
			<average value="0" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="16" name="rpgitem" friendlyname="RPG Item Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="1" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>