<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><items termsofuse="https://boardgamegeek.com/xmlapi/termsofuse"><item type="videogame" id="168553">
                                     				
				<name type="primary" sortindex="1" value="Zoo Park" />
			
						                           
						               													<description>Like any modern animal care facility in the 21st Century, you will need to run a professional programme of rescue, rehabilitation, research and conservation to promote understanding and care of all the animals under your control.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Of course, each animal type has its own list of requirements in terms of habitat, nutrition and care. You will need to address the individual needs of each one in order to run a successful and ethically sound zoo park.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Saying goodbye to the animals you have raised from new-borns is hard but as your sanctuary continues to grow, there will be plenty of new animals requiring rescue which you will be given the option to accept or not depending on your available resources at that time.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Be careful however. Expanding your sanctuary means that your workload will increase accordingly and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to be able to make sure your facility runs like clockwork in order to gain the all important popularity points from your visitors which determine the level of your success.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;As well as animal care, another main task of this management game is constructing a well thought out facility to best meet the requirements of both the animals and your visitors. You must construct the correctly sized habitats for each of your animals. A Koala bear won&amp;rsquo;t appreciate sharing an enclosed space with a tiger for example. Remember that each animal will also have several requirements which you&amp;rsquo;ll need to consider when mapping out your zoo park. Some species will favour a large pool of water to happily swim about in whilst others will enjoy a large amount of plant life to themselves. You&amp;rsquo;ll also need to consider their diet and how much space each animal will require. You&amp;rsquo;ll then need to hire staff to help you run the park.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;As well as keeping your animals happy, healthy and rehabilitating them into the wild, the hoards of visitors will also need to be accommodated by constructing pathways so that they can see your animals, building toilet facilities, constructing cafes and ice-cream stands and a gift shop.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Can you rescue, rehabilitate and research your animals to promote animal welfare education whilst constructing the ultimate zoo park to keep all your charges and visitors happy?&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Features of Zoo Park: Run Your Own Animal Sanctuary:&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;     The Zoo Park game is available for both PC and Mac&amp;#10;     You&amp;rsquo;ll care for over 30 animals from all four corners of the Earth&amp;#10;     Each animal type has its own list of requirements in terms of habitat, nutrition and care.&amp;#10;     Run a professional programme of rescue, rehabilitation, research and conservation to promote understanding and care of all the animals&amp;#10;     Make sure your facility runs like clockwork in order to gain the all important popularity points from your visitors&amp;#10;     Construct a well thought out park to best meet the requirements of both the animals and your visitors&amp;#10;     Build the correctly sized habitats for each of your animals&amp;#10;     Some species will favour a large pool of water to happily swim about in whilst others will enjoy a large amount of plant life to themselves&amp;#10;     You must consider diet and how much space each animal will require&amp;#10;     You&amp;rsquo;ll need to hire staff to help you run the park&amp;#10;     Construct pathways so that your visitors can see your animals as well as toilet facilities, cafes, ice-cream stands and a gift shop&amp;#10;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Source: The Developer Website.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;</description>
										      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4729" value="Macintosh" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogameplatform" id="4977" value="Windows" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamegenre" id="2156" value="Simulation" />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2471" value="Animals" />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogametheme" id="2511" value="Business / Construction" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamemode" id="2149" value="Single-Player" />
		
									
			

			               				<minplayers value="1" />
						               				<maxplayers value="1" />
						               				<releasedate value="2014-06-13" />
						      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamedeveloper" id="14732" value="Excalibur Publishing Ltd." />
		
									
			

			      				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="14732" value="Excalibur Publishing Ltd." />
		
									
				
		 			

			
		
					<link type="videogamepublisher" id="27412" value="Merge Games" />
		
									
			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			      			

			
	

	

	
	
	
   		<statistics page="1">
								<ratings >
			<usersrated value="1" />
			<average value="5" />
			<bayesaverage value="0" />

			<ranks>
															<rank type="subtype" id="32" name="videogame" friendlyname="Video Game Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
																				<rank type="family" id="4729" name="macintosh" friendlyname="Macintosh Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
											<rank type="family" id="4977" name="pc" friendlyname="Windows Rank" value="Not Ranked" bayesaverage="Not Ranked" />
												</ranks>

			<stddev value="0" />
			<median value="0" />
			<owned value="7" />
			<trading value="0" />
			<wanting value="0" />
			<wishing value="0" />
			<numcomments value="0" />
			<numweights value="0" />
			<averageweight value="0" />
			</ratings>
								</statistics>
     
	
          
</item>
</items>